<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mywebstore>
  <created_at>2026-07-07 12:00</created_at>
  <products>
    <product>
      <id>24000rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge Battery 20V 4Ah 80Wh, Bidirectional USB-C, LED, USB-C Cable
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-2400e-x-charge-863</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-2400e-x-charge-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-863.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery Tool Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>32.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>24000rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739030587</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge battery (20V, 4Ah, 80Wh) powers the entire RURIS 20V tool range. Its 21700 cells deliver up to 30% more runtime than standard batteries of the same format, and its bidirectional USB-C port lets you recharge it from any USB-C source or power your mobile devices. The ALFA UP system protects against critical discharge. Supplied with a 1 m USB-C cable.

• Battery and power bank in one: bidirectional USB-C port to recharge the battery without a dedicated charger and power smartphones or tablets directly, in the garden or on the go.
• Compatible with the RURIS 20V range: fits blowers, brush cutters, chainsaws, lawn mowers and other RURIS 20V cordless tools, with a light weight of just 0.64 kg.
• High-density 21700 cells: up to 30% more runtime than standard batteries of the same format, for extended work sessions.
• ALFA UP system: protection against critical discharge and battery recovery even after several months of storage, to safeguard your investment.
• Box contents: 1 ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge battery 20V 4Ah 80Wh with 3-level LED display and 1 USB-C to USB-C cable, 1 m.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>64000rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS ALFA UP 6400e VoltX Battery 60V 4Ah 240Wh, 21700 Cells, Digital Percentage Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-6400e-855</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-6400e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-855.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery Tool Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>129.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>64000rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020564</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ALFA UP 6400e battery (60V, 4Ah, 240Wh) powers the tools of the RURIS VoltX high-voltage platform: brush cutters, chainsaws, blowers. Its 21700 cells maintain constant torque in dense grass or hard wood, and its digital display shows the exact charge level in percent. The ALFA UP system enables recovery after 6 to 12 months of storage. Weight: 1.5 kg.

• 60V high-voltage platform: 240Wh to power RURIS VoltX tools at full power in dense grass, thick brush or hard wood, without any drop in speed.
• Digital percentage display: exact charge level from 1 to 100%, far more precise than a segmented LED indicator, so you can plan your sessions and avoid unexpected stops.
• New-generation 21700 cells: around 30% more runtime than standard 18650 cells, with a stable current flow under heavy load.
• ALFA UP system: protection against critical discharge and battery recovery after 6 to 12 months of storage in a discharged state, to protect your investment.
• Compatible with the VoltX 60V range: dedicated battery for brush cutters, chainsaws, blowers and other RURIS VoltX machines; controlled weight of 1.5 kg.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>68000rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS ALFA UP 6800e VoltX Battery 60V 8Ah 480Wh, 21700 Cells, Digital Percentage Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-6800e-856</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/acumulator-ruris-alfa-up-6800e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-856.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery Tool Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>169.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>68000rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020571</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ALFA UP 6800e battery (60V, 8Ah, 480Wh) is the maximum-runtime solution of the VoltX 60V platform, designed for intensive work on large areas. Its 21700 cells deliver stable current right to the end of discharge, and the digital display shows the exact charge level in percent. The ALFA UP system enables recovery after 6 to 12 months of storage. Weight: 2.7 kg.

• 480Wh of maximum runtime: 8Ah capacity for long, uninterrupted work sessions, ideal for large areas in sustained or semi-professional use.
• Stable current to the very end: the 21700 cells maintain motor speed even as the battery approaches 0%, for a clean cut down to the last metre.
• Digital percentage display: exact charge level from 1 to 100% to manage remaining runtime precisely and avoid any unexpected stop mid-task.
• ALFA UP system: protection against critical discharge and recovery after 6 to 12 months of storage in a discharged state, with no premature battery replacement.
• Compatible with the entire VoltX 60V range: brush cutters, chainsaws, blowers and other RURIS VoltX tools; rugged construction for intensive loads.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>ifh01-33h-13am</id>
      <name>RURIS Vulcano 300S – Electric Fan Heater 230 V, Adjustable Thermostat, for Workshop and
        Garage</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/incalzitoare/aeroterma-electrica-ruris-vulcano-300s-466</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aeroterma-electrica-ruris-vulcano-300s-pds-66-1920-1024-0-0-466.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aeroterma-electrica-ruris-vulcano-300s-pds-66-1920-1024-0-0-466_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Heating &gt; Electric Fan Heaters</category>
      <price_with_vat>45.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>ifh01-33h-13am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739067972</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Vulcano 300S electric fan heater quickly warms workshops, garages, greenhouses and work spaces thanks to its heating element and fan, which spread an even heat with no combustion and no smoke. The adjustable thermostat maintains the desired temperature and prevents excessive energy consumption. Compact and fitted with a handle, it moves easily to wherever it is needed.

• Instant heat without combustion: the electric heating element and fan quickly spread even heat, with no smoke and no fuel to store.
• Versatile: ideal for spot heating of workshops, garages, greenhouses and work spaces, and for protecting crops from frost.
• Adjustable thermostat: automatically maintains the desired temperature and limits energy consumption; several heat levels available.
• Compact and mobile: small footprint with a carry handle to move it easily from room to room and store it without clutter.
• Simple to use: runs on 230 V mains power with no installation required; just plug it in and enjoy instant heat.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>80240rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 8024e – Cordless Pressure Washer 20V, 30 Bar, 5 L/min, Self-Priming, USB-C Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/aparat-de-splat-cu-presiune-pe-acumulator-ruris-8024e-865</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-de-splat-cu-presiune-pe-acumulator-ruris-8024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-865.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-de-splat-cu-presiune-pe-acumulator-ruris-8024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-865_8.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>85.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>80240rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033403</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 8024e cordless pressure washer is completely self-sufficient: its self-priming system with float draws water from a bucket, a canister or any water source, with no tap and no power outlet needed. With 30 bar and a 5 L/min flow rate, it cleans your car, bike, garden furniture and tools. Ultra-light (1.5 kg), supplied in a carry case with a 6-in-1 nozzle and a RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with USB-C charging included.

• Effective pressure: 20V brushless motor delivering up to 30 bar and 5 L/min for fast cleaning of lightly to moderately soiled surfaces.
• Total independence: self-priming system with 5 m hose, filter and float to draw water from a bucket, a canister or a pool, no tap required.
• Adjustable 6-in-1 nozzle: switch from a concentrated jet to a wide spray with a simple twist; pinpoint/fan jet nozzle and foam container included.
• Ultra-portable: just 1.5 kg, easy to handle with one hand, ideal for camping, the car park or mountain biking, supplied with a carry case.
• Battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>as140m2022am</id>
      <name>RURIS AS140MMA – Inverter Welding Machine 140A, MMA, Hot Start, Anti Stick, Arc Force,
        Digital Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-sudura/aparat-sudura-ruris-as140mma-457</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as140mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-457.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as140mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-457_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Welding Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>95.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>as140m2022am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000054</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AS140MMA inverter welding machine delivers up to 140 A for MMA welding with coated electrodes (1.6 to 3.2 mm) on all types of steel. Its Hot Start, Anti Stick and Arc Force functions make striking the arc easier and keep it stable, while the digital display allows precise current adjustment. Compact (4.9 kg), it comes with a mask, clamps, hammer/brush, 2.5 mm rutile electrodes (2.5 kg) and a magnetic square.

• 140 A inverter with digital display: precise current control for clean, even weld seams on all types of steel.
• Smart functions: Hot Start for easy arc ignition, Anti Stick to prevent electrode sticking and Arc Force for a stable arc even at short distance.
• Electrodes from 1.6 to 3.2 mm: compatible with rutile and basic electrodes, for repairs, the workshop, the farm and DIY at home.
• Light and mobile: only 4.9 kg, with handle and carry strap so you can weld anywhere, powered from 230 V mains.
• Box contents: welding machine, mask, hammer/brush, earth clamp, electrode holder, 2.5 mm rutile electrodes (2.5 kg) and magnetic square.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>as180m2022am</id>
      <name>RURIS AS180MMA – Inverter Welding Machine 180A, MMA, Hot Start, Anti Stick, Arc Force,
        Digital Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-sudura/aparat-sudura-ruris-as180mma-459</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as180mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-459.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as180mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-459_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Welding Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>as180m2022am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000078</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AS180MMA inverter welding machine delivers up to 180 A for MMA welding with coated electrodes from 2.5 to 4 mm on various types of steel. Hot Start, Anti Stick and Arc Force guarantee instant arc ignition and a stable arc, with a digital display for precise current adjustment. Lightweight (5.1 kg), it comes with two masks, gloves, hammer/brush, clamps and 3.2 mm electrodes (2.5 kg). Ideal for the workshop, the farm and maintenance work.

• 180 A inverter with digital display: precise electronic current control for clean, reliable welds, even on demanding jobs.
• Advanced functions: Hot Start for instant arc ignition, Anti Stick to prevent electrode sticking and Arc Force for perfect stability with a short arc.
• Electrodes from 2.5 to 4 mm: compatible with rutile and basic electrodes, suited to different steels and welding applications in the workshop or on site.
• Compact and portable: only 5.1 kg, with handle and strap for easy transport, powered from 230 V mains.
• Box contents: standard mask and professional mask, hammer/brush, earth clamp, electrode holder, 3.2 mm electrodes (2.5 kg) and welding gloves.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>as200m2022am</id>
      <name>RURIS AS200MMA – Inverter Welding Machine 200A, MMA, Hot Start, Anti Stick, Arc Force,
        Digital Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-sudura/aparat-sudura-ruris-as200mma-461</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as200mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-461.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparat-sudura-ruris-as200mma-pds-78-1920-1024-0-0-461_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Welding Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>152.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>as200m2022am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000092</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AS200MMA inverter welding machine delivers up to 200 A for coated-electrode welding (2.5 to 4 mm) of stainless steel, alloy steel or carbon steel. Hot Start, Anti Stick and Arc Force ensure fast arc ignition and a stable arc, with a digital display for precise current control. Compact (5.6 kg), it comes fully equipped: masks, gloves, apron, clamps, hammer/brush, 3.2 mm electrodes (2.5 kg) and a magnetic square.

• 200 A inverter with digital display: high power and precise current control for durable welds on a wide range of metals.
• Smart functions: Hot Start for fast arc ignition, Anti Stick to prevent electrode sticking and Arc Force for smooth welding even with a short arc.
• Electrodes from 2.5 to 4 mm: rutile and basic, for welding stainless steel, alloy steel, carbon steel and other common metals.
• Compact and rugged: 5.6 kg, ergonomic design with handle and strap, ideal in the workshop, on the farm or at home, powered from 230 V mains.
• Box contents: standard and professional masks, gloves, apron, hammer/brush, clamps, 3.2 mm electrodes (2.5 kg) and magnetic square.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>34500asp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS OS345 – Oscillating Garden Sprinkler 345 m², 18 Adjustable Nozzles, 110° Angle,
        Adjustable Flow</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/aspersor-ruris-os345-785</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aspersor-ruris-os345-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-785_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/717lqBYLP+L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>29.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>34500asp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002430</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS OS345 oscillating sprinkler waters lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens evenly, with coverage of up to 345 m². Its 18 flexible nozzles with adjustable direction and its oscillation angle of up to 110° let you fine-tune the watered area, while the adjustable flow rate adapts to the weather. Built from aluminium, ABS and POM, lightweight (0.68 kg), it operates at a water pressure of 2 to 4 bar.

• Wide coverage: up to 345 m² watered thanks to 18 flexible plastic nozzles and an adjustable oscillation angle of up to 110°.
• Precise control: adjustable flow rate and adjustable nozzle direction to match the watering to the shape of your garden and the weather.
• Durable construction: body made of aluminium, ABS and POM combining strength and light weight (0.68 kg), dimensions 47.3 x 12.9 x 9.7 cm.
• Easy maintenance: nozzle-cleaning needle built into the end of the oscillating tube for consistent performance over time.
• Ready to use: adapter included for quick connection to the hose; operates from 2 to 4 bar and from 5 to 35 °C.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20000asp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS UFO200 – Rotating Sprinkler for Lawns and Vegetable Gardens, Adjustable Range,
        Quick Hose Connection</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/aspersor-ruris-ufo200-786</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aspersor-ruris-ufo200-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-786_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/aspersor-ruris-ufo200-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-786.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>21.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20000asp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002447</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS UFO200 rotating sprinkler distributes water evenly over lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens thanks to its steady rotation. Its adjustable range lets you set the watered area for even irrigation with no supervision. It connects to the garden hose in one simple move and runs on mains water pressure, with no electricity, for easy care of your green spaces.

• Even watering by rotation: distributes water uniformly over a large circular area, for lawns watered with no dry spots.
• Versatile: suitable for lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens; waters unattended while you get on with other tasks.
• Adjustable range: the watered zone adjusts to the area to be covered, saving water and precisely targeting your plantings.
• No electricity: works solely on mains water pressure; lightweight, simple to set up and move around the garden.
• Box contents: UFO200 rotating sprinkler, connecting directly to a standard garden hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>45000asp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS ZN450 – Oscillating Sprinkler for Large Lawns, Adjustable Watering Width, Quick
        Connection</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/aspersor-ruris-zn450-787</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/aspersor-ruris-zn450-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-787_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/aspersor-ruris-zn450-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-787_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>12.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>45000asp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002454</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ZN450 oscillating sprinkler covers large rectangular areas with a steady sweeping motion, ideal for lawns and vegetable gardens. Its adjustable watering width lets you match the covered zone to your plot and spread the water evenly, with no dry patches. It connects quickly to the garden hose and works on mains water pressure alone, with no electricity.

• Wide, even coverage: oscillating sweep that waters large rectangular areas with no dry spots, for a green, even lawn.
• Versatile in the garden: ideal for large lawns, vegetable gardens and flower beds, with no supervision needed while watering.
• Adjustable watering width: the covered zone adjusts to the shape and size of the plot, avoiding water waste.
• Simple and reliable: runs on mains water pressure, with no electrical parts; lightweight and easy to move from one area to another.
• Box contents: ZN450 oscillating sprinkler, connecting directly to a standard garden hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>99000ARS25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS AR99S Portable Electric Mist Blower 99000ARS25A, Attachment for Electric Sprayers, Garden Treatments</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/atomizor-electric-portabil-ruris-ar99s-657</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/atomizor-electric-portabil-ruris-ar99s-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-657.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Mist Blowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>21.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>99000ARS25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739067989</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AR99s portable electric mist blower sprays a fine mist that covers foliage evenly: ideal for plant protection treatments, liquid fertilisers and disinfection in the garden, orchard or vineyard. Lightweight (1.95 kg) and easy to handle, it runs on a built-in rechargeable battery, supplied with the unit, so you can treat crops and green spaces cordlessly and effortlessly.

• Fine covering mist: spreads the product evenly over foliage for effective plant protection treatments and liquid fertiliser applications.
• Versatile: suited to the garden, orchard and vineyard, as well as space disinfection, for gardeners, fruit growers and winegrowers.
• Built-in rechargeable battery included: cord-free runtime to treat freely, with no fuel mixing and no emissions.
• Light and easy to handle: just 1.95 kg, a handheld format for long spraying sessions without fatigue, with an effective reach over crops.
• Ready to use: integrated product tank and fine-mist spray nozzle for even application from the very first use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10912020am</id>
      <name>RURIS A109S – Petrol Backpack Mist Blower 3HP, 14L Tank, 12 m Range + Protective
        Equipment Kit</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/atomizoare/atomizor-ruris-a109s-380</link>
      <image>
        http://feed.ruris.ro/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/detaliu-a109s-5.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Mist Blowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>184.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10912020am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002003</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS A109S petrol backpack mist blower features a 3 HP 2-stroke engine and a 14 L tank compatible with both liquids and granules. Its 12 m horizontal range (10 m vertical), 4 spray levels and 90° booster pump treat orchards, vineyards and field crops effectively. Padded shoulder straps and a START/STOP handle for comfort. Supplied with a protection kit: mask, goggles, coveralls and ear defenders.

• 3 HP 2-stroke petrol engine: electronic ignition, 1.4 L fuel tank and 100 km/h air outlet speed for powerful spraying.
• Long range: 12 m horizontal and 10 m vertical, with a booster pump enabling spraying at 90°, ideal for treating trees.
• Versatile 14 L tank: compatible with liquids and granules, 4 spray levels (mist, droplets, jet) and a 6-hole injector nozzle kit.
• Carrying comfort: padded shoulder straps, cushioned back panel and ergonomic multifunction START/STOP handle for long treatment sessions.
• Box contents: mist blower, liquid filter and 6-hole nozzle kit, plus a protection kit with mask, goggles, coveralls and ear defenders.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>25050rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX25050 – SDS MAX Demolition Hammer 1700 W, 45 J, 2100 bpm, Anti-Vibration + 2
        Chisels</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/ciocan-rotopercutor-pentru-demolari-581</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-pentru-demolari-pds-86-1920-1024-0-0-581.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>179.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>25050rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739061734</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX25050 demolition hammer delivers 45 J of impact energy at 2100 blows per minute thanks to its 1700 W motor with copper windings. With its SDS MAX chuck, 360° rotating handle, adjustable speed and anti-vibration system, it makes short work of reinforced concrete, masonry and stone. Supplied with an 18 mm pointed chisel and flat chisel, spare carbon brushes, grease and an Allen key.

• 45 J of impact at 2100 blows/min: 1700 W motor with copper windings to demolish reinforced concrete, masonry and stone.
• Professional SDS MAX chuck: stable, rugged chisel mounting, with fast tool-free accessory changes.
• Adjustable speed and Lock-On function: impact intensity matched to the material and a locked switch for continuous work.
• Enhanced comfort: 360° rotating auxiliary handle and an anti-vibration system that reduces fatigue over long sessions.
• Complete kit included: 18 mm pointed chisel, 18 mm flat chisel, auxiliary handle, spare carbon brushes, tube of grease and Allen key.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12100RMX26B</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1210 – Cordless SDS Plus Rotary Hammer 20V, 1.5 J, LED, 20V 4Ah USB-C Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-604</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-604.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-604_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>90.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12100RMX26B</mpn>
      <ean>5940739064377</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1210 SDS Plus cordless rotary hammer drills into concrete up to 16 mm, wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm thanks to its 1.5 J of impact energy, 900 rpm and 5100 blows/min. Compact (1.4 kg), with variable speed, reverse function and LED light. Supplied with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging (cable included, no mains charger required) and 3 SDS Plus drill bits, 8/10/12 mm.

• SDS Plus drilling and hammer action: 1.5 J of impact energy, 900 rpm and 5100 blows/min to drill concrete up to 16 mm, wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm.
• 20V 4Ah battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e battery with bidirectional USB-C charging, rechargeable from any USB-C port and usable as a power bank for your mobile devices.
• Quick-lock SDS Plus chuck: tool-free bit changes, variable speed and reverse function for total drilling control.
• Compact and easy to handle: just 1.4 kg with a built-in LED light, ideal for fixing shelves, curtain rails and light fittings into concrete or brick.
• Box contents: RMX1210 rotary hammer, 20V 4Ah USB-C battery with cable, 3 SDS Plus drill bits (8/10/12 mm); USB-C charging with no dedicated mains charger.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>28130rmx26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX2813 – Brushless SDS Plus Rotary Hammer Drill 20V, 2.8 J, 20V 4Ah USB-C Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/search/rmx2813</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx2813-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-605.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx2813-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-605_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>116.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>28130rmx26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033359</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX2813 cordless rotary hammer drill with brushless motor drills concrete up to 26 mm, wood up to 30 mm and metal up to 13 mm with 2.8 J of impact energy. Four functions: drilling, hammer drilling, chiselling and VarioLock. Supplied with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging (cable included, no mains charger), 3 SDS Plus drill bits and a depth stop.

• Brushless power: 2.8 J of impact, 1150 rpm and 5100 blows/min to drill concrete up to 26 mm, wood up to 30 mm and metal up to 13 mm without losing speed.
• 20V 4Ah battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e battery with bidirectional USB-C charging, rechargeable from any USB-C port and usable as a power bank for your mobile devices.
• 4 functions including VarioLock: drilling, hammer drilling and chiselling, with chisel locking at the optimal angle to break tiles or remove mortar with precision.
• Controlled work: depth stop, variable speed and LED light for consistent drilling; well-balanced 2.7 kg weight.
• Box contents: RMX2813 rotary hammer, 20V 4Ah USB-C battery with cable, 3 SDS Plus drill bits (8/10/12 mm), depth stop; USB-C charging without a mains charger.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>4526rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX4526 – SDS Plus Rotary Hammer Drill 1050W, 4.5 J, 3 Functions, Concrete
        Drilling + Accessories</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/ciocan-rotopercutor-sds-plus-ruris-rmx4526-583</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-sds-plus-ruris-rmx4526-pds-86-1920-1024-0-0-583.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>69.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>4526rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739061758</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX4526 rotary hammer drill combines three functions: normal drilling, hammer drilling and chiselling. Its 1050 W motor with copper winding delivers 4.5 J at 4200 blows per minute, with a drilling capacity in concrete of up to 42 mm. Lightweight (4.5 kg) and ergonomic, it comes with pointed and flat 14 mm chisels, 3 SDS Plus drill bits, a depth stop and maintenance accessories.

• 1050 W motor with copper winding: 4.5 J of impact energy at 4200 blows/min for drilling and chiselling concrete, masonry and stone.
• 3 functions in 1: normal drilling, hammer drilling and chiselling to cover the majority of construction jobs.
• Quick-change SDS Plus chuck: accessories swapped without tools, with concrete drilling up to 42 mm.
• Refined ergonomics: only 4.5 kg, vibration-absorbing handle and depth stop for consistent drilling.
• Complete kit: pointed and flat 14 mm chisels, 3 drill bits 8/10/12 mm, auxiliary handle, carbon brushes, dust guard, grease and wrench.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2400plus21am</id>
      <name>RURIS AirPower 2400PLUS – Air Compressor 1500W 2HP, 24L Tank, 8 bar, 180 L/min +
        Accessory Kit</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/compresoare-aer/pachet-compresor-kit-accesorii-2400plus-413</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pachet-compresor-kit-accesorii-2400plus-pds-73-720-480-0-0-413_1.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Air Compressors</category>
      <price_with_vat>151.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2400plus21am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000115</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AirPower 2400PLUS piston air compressor pairs a 230 V electric motor rated at 1500 W (2 HP) with a 24 L tank, delivering a maximum pressure of 8 bar and an air flow of 180 L/min. Copper tubes, two outlets with individual pressure gauges, a noise-reducing cover and 5-inch wheels for mobility. Supplied as a pack with an accessory kit: blow gun, paint spray gun, washing gun, inflation gun and spiral hose.

• Solid performance: 1500 W (2 HP) electric motor at 2850 rpm, maximum pressure of 8 bar and air flow up to 180 L/min for common pneumatic tools.
• Versatile every day: inflating, blowing, painting, washing and cleaning in the workshop, garage or at home thanks to the supplied accessory kit.
• Two air outlets with individual pressure gauges: precisely controlled pressure and the option to connect two tools, with durable copper air tubes.
• Comfort and mobility: cover reducing piston noise, ergonomic handle and 5-inch wheels to move the 24 L tank easily.
• Box contents: compressor, blow gun, paint spray gun, washing gun, inflation gun and spiral hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>24000SIP25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS Silent Power 2400 – Silent Oil-Free Compressor 1500W, 24L Tank, 236 L/min, 8 bar</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/compresoare-aer/compresor-aer-ruris-silent-power-2400-oilfree-735</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/compresor-aer-ruris-silent-power-2400-oilfree-pds-73-1920-1024-0-0-735.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Air Compressors</category>
      <price_with_vat>166.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>24000SIP25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739063318</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Silent Power 2400OilFree silent oil-free compressor delivers clean compressed air thanks to its oil-free technology: ideal for workshops, garages and noise-sensitive spaces. Its 1500 W (2 HP) motor on 230 V drives 2 cylinders for a flow rate of 236 L/min, with a 24 L tank and a maximum pressure of 8 bar. Two outlets with independent pressure gauges, overload and overheating protection, 5-inch wheels and a detachable handle. 22 kg.

• High flow rate of 236 L/min: 1500 W (2 HP) motor and 2 cylinders for fast, even compression, 24 L tank and maximum pressure of 8 bar.
• Oil-free, clean air: no oil changes or lubrication, compressed air free of contaminants, suited to workshops, clinics, laboratories and commercial spaces.
• Two independent outlets with individual pressure gauges: power two pneumatic tools at the same time with separately set pressures.
• Enhanced safety: motor overload and overheating protection, built-in safety valve for intensive, risk-free use.
• Mobile and compact: sturdy 5-inch wheels, detachable handle with hose holder and a contained weight of 22 kg for easy movement around the workshop.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>50000SIP25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS Silent Power 5000 – Silent Oil-Free Compressor 1500W, 50L Tank, 236 L/min, 8 bar</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/compresoare-aer/compresor-aer-ruris-silent-power-5000-oilfree-736</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/compresor-aer-ruris-silent-power-5000-oilfree-pds-73-1920-1024-0-0-736.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Air Compressors</category>
      <price_with_vat>194.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>50000SIP25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739063325</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Silent Power 5000OilFree silent oil-free compressor combines a large 50 L tank with a 236 L/min flow rate for a continuous air supply, even during prolonged use. Its 1500 W (2 HP) motor on 230 V drives 2 cylinders and delivers up to 8 bar, with no oil and no contaminants. Two outlets with independent pressure gauges, overload and overheating protection, large 6-inch wheels and a detachable handle. 28 kg.

• Long-lasting air supply: 50 L tank, 236 L/min flow rate and maximum pressure of 8 bar to power paint spray guns, impact drivers and inflators without interruption.
• Oil-free, clean air: no oil changes or lubrication, compressed air free of contaminants, ideal for workshops, garages, clinics and noise-sensitive laboratories.
• Two independent outlets with individual pressure gauges: two pneumatic tools powered simultaneously with separately set pressures.
• Enhanced safety: motor overload and overheating protection, built-in safety valve for intensive, prolonged use.
• Optimal mobility: large 6-inch wheels for rolling over uneven surfaces, detachable handle with hose holder, a well-balanced 28 kg.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12000lux25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Luxury12 – Garden Hose Connector 1/2", Watertight Quick Coupling, Non-Slip</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/conector-furtun-ruris-luxury-12-788</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-ruris-luxury-12-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-788.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>7.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12000lux25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002713</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Luxury12 connector provides a fast, watertight connection for 1/2 inch garden hoses. It clips on in one move to attach a spray gun, lance or sprinkler to the garden hose, with no leaks and no tools. Its non-slip surface makes handling easy even with wet hands, and its sturdy construction makes it compatible with standard watering systems.

• Quick coupling: clips onto a 1/2 inch garden hose in one move to connect a spray gun, lance or sprinkler.
• Reliable watertightness: leak-free connection for efficient watering and a constant water flow.
• Secure grip: non-slip surface for easy connecting and disconnecting, even with wet hands.
• Sturdy and compatible: durable construction, compatible with standard watering fittings and systems.
• Tool-free installation: immediate setup, a lightweight (0.07 kg) and practical accessory for everyday use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>34000lux25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Luxury34 – Garden Hose Connector 3/4", Watertight Quick Coupling, High Flow Rates</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/conector-furtun-ruris-luxury-34-789</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-ruris-luxury-34-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-789_3.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-ruris-luxury-34-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-789_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>6.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>34000lux25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002720</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Luxury34 connector provides a fast, watertight connection for 3/4 inch garden hoses. Designed for high flow rates, it clips onto the hose in one move to attach a spray gun, lance or tap, with no leaks and no tools. Its sturdy construction and non-slip surface guarantee a reliable connection, compatible with standard watering systems.

• Built for high flow rates: 3/4 inch format offering a greater water passage than 1/2 inch, ideal for large areas.
• Quick coupling: clips onto the hose in one move to connect a spray gun, lance or tap, with tool-free fitting and removal.
• Reinforced watertightness: reliable, leak-free connection, compatible with standard watering systems.
• Ergonomic and durable: non-slip surface for a secure grip even with wet hands; sturdy construction for intensive use.
• Box contents: Luxury34 connector for 3/4 inch garden hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12000lxy25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Luxury12 – Aquastop Stop Connector for 1/2" Garden Hose, Automatic Water Shut-Off</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-12-790</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-12-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-790.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-12-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-790_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>7.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12000lxy25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002737</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Luxury12 stop connector for 1/2 inch garden hoses features an aquastop system that automatically cuts off the water as soon as the accessory is disconnected. No more splashing and no more waste: swap spray guns or lances without turning off the tap. Sturdy and watertight, it clips on in one move and remains compatible with standard watering systems.

• Automatic water shut-off: the aquastop system stops the water the moment the accessory is disconnected, with no splashing or waste.
• Easy accessory changes: switch from spray gun to lance or sprinkler without going back to turn off the tap.
• Standard 1/2 inch format: clips onto the garden hose in one move and remains compatible with standard fittings.
• Sturdy and watertight: resistant construction with a non-slip surface for easy handling even with wet hands.
• Box contents: Luxury12 aquastop stop connector for 1/2 inch hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>34000lxy25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Luxury34 – Aquastop Stop Connector for 3/4" Garden Hose, Automatic Water Shut-Off</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-34-791</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-34-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-791_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/conector-furtun-stop-ruris-luxury-34-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-791_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>7.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>34000lxy25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002744</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Luxury34 stop connector for 3/4 inch garden hoses is fitted with an aquastop system that automatically cuts off the water when the accessory is disconnected. Ideal for high flow rates, it lets you swap spray guns or lances without turning off the tap and without splashing. Sturdy and watertight, it clips on in one move and suits standard watering systems.

• Automatic water shut-off: the aquastop stops the water as soon as the accessory is disconnected, with no splashing or waste.
• High-flow 3/4 inch format: designed for large-diameter hoses, with a greater water passage than the 1/2 inch format.
• Effortless accessory changes: replace the spray gun, lance or sprinkler without going back to turn off the tap.
• Sturdy and watertight: resistant construction with a non-slip surface for safe handling and a reliable, leak-free connection.
• Box contents: Luxury34 aquastop stop connector for 3/4 inch hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10061cdp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS SmartYD 100M – Waterproof Garden Storage Box, Galvanised Steel, 300L, 80 kg Bench,
        Anthracite</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/cutii-depozitare/cutie-depozitare-ruris-smartyd-100m-732</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-smartyd-100m-storage-box-pds-97-1920-1024-0-0-732.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-smartyd-100m-storage-box-pds-97-1920-1024-0-0-732_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Storage Boxes</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10061cdp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002751</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS SmartYD 100M storage box protects cushions, tools and garden accessories from moisture, dust and UV thanks to its waterproof galvanised steel. Its 300 L capacity, gas-strut lid that holds in 2 positions and cylinder lock with 2 keys keep your storage secure on the patio, in the garden or in the garage. Supporting 80 kg on the lid, it also doubles as a bench. Dimensions: 100 x 61 x 62 cm, anthracite grey.

• 300 L of waterproof storage: galvanised steel resistant to weather and UV, where plastic boxes fade and become brittle in the sun.
• Versatile outdoors and indoors: stores outdoor cushions, garden tools, pool equipment and seasonal accessories away from moisture.
• Gas-strut lid: assisted opening with 2 holding positions and a T-handle, cylinder lock supplied with 2 keys to secure the contents.
• Doubles as a bench: structure supporting up to 80 kg on the lid, a handy extra seat on the patio, dimensions 100 x 61 x 62 cm.
• Durable and easy to live with: discreet anthracite grey finish, simple assembly and easy maintenance for many years of outdoor use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>13061cdp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS SmartYD 130M – Waterproof Garden Storage Box, Galvanised Steel, 400L, 80 kg Bench,
        Anthracite</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/cutii-depozitare/cutie-depozitare-ruris-smartyd-130m-733</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-smartyd-130m-storage-box-pds-97-1920-1024-0-0-733.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-smartyd-130m-storage-box-pds-97-1920-1024-0-0-733_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Storage Boxes</category>
      <price_with_vat>129.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>13061cdp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739002768</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS SmartYD 130M storage box is the large version of the range: 400 L in waterproof galvanised steel to protect cushions, tools and equipment from moisture, dust and UV. Gas-strut lid that holds in 2 positions, T-handle and cylinder lock with 2 keys for secure storage in the garden, on the patio or in the garage. It supports 80 kg and also doubles as a bench. Dimensions: 130 x 61 x 62 cm, anthracite grey.

• 400 L of waterproof storage: large version in galvanised steel resistant to weather and UV, where plastic boxes warp in the sun.
• Large family-sized capacity: stores outdoor cushions, garden tools, pool equipment and seasonal accessories, indoors or outdoors.
• Gas-strut lid: assisted opening with 2 holding positions and a T-handle, cylinder lock supplied with 2 keys to secure the contents.
• Doubles as a bench: structure supporting up to 80 kg on the lid, a handy extra seat, generous dimensions of 130 x 61 x 62 cm.
• Durable and easy to live with: discreet anthracite grey finish, simple assembly and easy maintenance for long-lasting outdoor use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>25240RUR26B</id>
      <name>RURIS 2524e – Brushless Cordless Chainsaw 20V 4Ah, 250 mm Bar, Lightweight 3.1 kg,
        Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2524e-563</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2524e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-563.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71SzAW4W4PL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>90.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>25240RUR26B</mpn>
      <ean>5940739064407</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2524e cordless chainsaw is a compact brushless model weighing 3.1 kg with a 250 mm bar and a maximum cutting capacity of 245 mm, designed for pruning fruit trees and cutting light firewood. Quiet and free of petrol-engine maintenance, it is perfectly suited to residential areas. ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery included, with bidirectional USB-C charging: no mains charger needed.

• Compact and efficient: 20V 4Ah (80 Wh) brushless motor and 250 mm bar for cutting branches, hardwood and logs up to 245 mm.
• Ideal in the orchard and garden: pruning fruit trees and cutting light firewood, with no cable, fuel mix or exhaust fumes.
• Automatic lubrication: generous 220 ml oil tank for continuous protection of the chain and bar.
• Light and quiet: only 3.1 kg for optimal handling and use in residential areas without noise nuisance.
• USB-C battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery rechargeable from any USB-C port and usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>26240rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 2624e – Battery Chainsaw 20V 4Ah, 300 mm Bar, Tool-Free SDS, USB-C Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2624e-867</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2624e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-867.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2624e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-867_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>26240rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033397</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2624e cordless chainsaw runs on a 20V 4Ah battery and offers a 300 mm bar with a maximum cutting capacity of 275 mm, ideal for garden maintenance, pruning and cutting light firewood. Tool-free SDS chain tensioning, safety brake and automatic lubrication (210 ml tank). ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge battery included, rechargeable via USB-C.

• Instant start: 20V electric motor at 3,600 rpm and a chain speed of 7 m/s for cutting branches, logs and small trunks without cable or fuel.
• Easier garden maintenance: perfect for pruning, trimming fruit trees and cutting light firewood around the house.
• Tool-free SDS tensioning: chain adjustable in seconds right at the worksite, automatic lubrication with a 210 ml oil tank.
• Safe operation: mechanical chain brake with emergency stop and unlock button for constant control.
• Battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah X-Charge Li-Ion battery with USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank for your mobile devices.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>27440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 2744e – Brushless Chainsaw 2x20V (40V), 400 mm Bar, 25 m/s, 2 x 4Ah Batteries
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-869</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-869.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-869.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>179.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>27440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033458</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2744e cordless chainsaw is driven by a brushless motor powered by 2 x 20V 4Ah batteries (40V, 160 Wh): 400 mm bar, maximum cutting capacity of 395 mm and a chain speed of 25 m/s for firewood and demanding pruning. Two speeds, tool-free SDS tensioning, double brake and low vibrations. The 2 included ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge batteries recharge via USB-C.

• 40V power: brushless motor at 13,500 rpm powered by 2 x 20V 4Ah batteries for a 25 m/s chain speed and fast cuts up to 395 mm.
• 2 speeds with variable trigger: match the power to thin branches or hardwood and optimise working runtime.
• Tool-free SDS tensioning: chain adjustment and replacement without a wrench or screwdriver, automatic lubrication with a 180 ml tank.
• Comfort and safety: double chain brake, reduced vibrations (1.76 m/s²) and a controlled weight of 5 kg for prolonged work without fatigue.
• 2 batteries included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah X-Charge Li-Ion batteries with USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>28440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 2844e – Lightweight 3.8 kg Brushless Chainsaw 2x20V (40V), 300 mm Bar, 2 Batteries
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-871</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-871.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-871.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>189.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>28440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033465</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[At just 3.8 kg, the RURIS 2844e cordless chainsaw is one of the lightest in its 40V class: a brushless motor powered by 2 x 20V 4Ah batteries, a 300 mm bar and a maximum cutting capacity of 285 mm for pruning and trimming trees, even at height. Tool-free SDS tensioning, double chain brake and automatic lubrication. 2 ALFA UP 2400e X-Charge batteries included, with USB-C charging.

• Record-breaking lightness: only 3.8 kg for a 2x20V (40V, 160 Wh) brushless motor, ideal for cutting branches and small trunks with total control.
• Effortless pruning: perfect for fruit trees, thick hedges and high branches, with push-button start and quiet operation.
• Tool-free SDS tensioning: chain adjustment in seconds, automatic lubrication with a 150 ml oil tank, chain speed of 6.7 m/s.
• Enhanced safety: double chain brake and a brushless motor delivering stable torque at full load, without overheating.
• 2 batteries included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah X-Charge Li-Ion batteries with USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>45640rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS VoltX 4564e – 60V Cordless Chainsaw, 450 mm Bar, 25 m/s, Battery and Charger
        Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-voltx-4564e-857</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-voltx-4564e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-857_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-voltx-4564e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-857_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>275.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>45640rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033526</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS VoltX 4564e cordless chainsaw combines a 60V brushless motor with a 450 mm bar and a chain speed of 25 m/s to cut firewood, medium-sized trunks and thick branches. Tool-free SDS tensioning, dual chain brake and LED lighting for safe, precise work. Supplied with the ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah battery and charger included.

• High cutting power: 60V brushless motor at 13,800 rpm, 450 mm bar and 25 m/s chain speed to cut through trunks up to 390 mm in a single pass.
• Versatile for everyday use: ideal for firewood, pruning and felling small trees, with no fuel mixing and no cable.
• Tool-free SDS adjustment: chain tensioning in seconds, automatic lubrication with a 240 ml oil tank and LED work light.
• Safety and comfort: dual chain brake, metal bucking spikes, Soft Grip handle and a contained weight of 4 kg for total control.
• Battery and charger included: RURIS ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah Li-Ion battery with digital display, compatible with the entire VoltX range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>14240rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 1424e – 20V Cordless Telescopic Pole Pruner, 1.29-1.70 m, 100 mm Cut, 4Ah Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-telescopic-ruris-1424e-567</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-telescopic-ruris-1424e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-567.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71wuNKmtRNL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>88.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>14240rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034707</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1424e cordless telescopic pole pruner lets you trim high branches from the ground thanks to its arm adjustable from 1.29 m to 1.70 m, with no ladder needed. Its 7-position pivoting head adapts to the orientation of the branches and cuts up to 100 mm, ideal for fruit and ornamental trees. Lightweight (2.5 kg), it comes with the ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with USB-C charging.

• Prune at height without a ladder: telescopic arm adjustable from 1.29 m to 1.70 m to safely reach high branches from the ground.
• Versatile in the orchard: ideal for maintaining fruit trees, ornamental trees and tall hedges, cutting branches up to 100 mm.
• 7-position pivoting head: adjustable cutting angle to match the orientation of the branches, with automatic chain lubrication.
• Light and easy to handle: around 2.5 kg with an ergonomic multi-point handle to reduce fatigue during extended work.
• USB-C battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery rechargeable from any USB-C port, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>31400RMX26B</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3140 – 20V Cordless Circular Saw, 140 mm Blade, 50 mm Cutting Depth, 0-45°,
        Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-602</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-602.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-602_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>99.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>31400RMX26B</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033380</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3140 cordless circular saw with a 20V brushless motor spins at 6800 rpm with a 140 mm blade to cut wood, MDF, OSB and certain plastics. Cutting depth adjustable up to 50 mm and angle adjustable from 0 to 45° for bevel cuts. Lightweight (1.8 kg), with LED light and graduated base plate. Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with USB-C charging and cable.

• 6800 rpm brushless motor: 140 mm blade for clean, fast cuts in wood, MDF, OSB and certain plastics, with no cord or power outlet.
• Ideal for DIY and home improvement: cuts boards, skirting, panels and battens, even at height or in tight spaces thanks to its 1.8 kg weight.
• Precise, adjustable cuts: depth up to 50 mm, angle adjustable from 0 to 45°, graduated base plate and width limiter for straight and bevel cuts.
• Comfort and visibility: LED lighting for poorly lit areas and a lightweight grip for long working sessions without fatigue.
• Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C port and cable; 140 mm blade fitted; the battery also powers your other RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>32600rmx26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3260 – 20V Brushless Cordless Jigsaw, 3800 rpm, 20V 4Ah USB-C Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-603</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-603.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-603_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>101.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>32600rmx26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033373</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3260 cordless jigsaw with a brushless motor cuts wood, metal, plastic and aluminium with precision: 3800 rpm, 26 mm stroke, 5 speeds plus automatic mode, 4 pendulum positions and an angle adjustable to ±45°. Easy Lock system and LED lighting. Supplied with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging (cable included, no mains charger) and 4 blades.

• Fast, clean cuts: brushless motor at 3800 rpm with a 26 mm blade stroke to cut wood, metal, plastic and aluminium with precision.
• 20V 4Ah battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e battery with bidirectional USB-C charging, rechargeable from any USB-C port and usable as a power bank for your mobile devices.
• Complete adjustments: 5 speeds plus automatic mode, 4 pendulum positions and cutting angle adjustable to ±22.5° and ±45° to suit every material.
• Cutting line always visible: automatic dust blowing, LED lighting and Easy Lock system to change blades in seconds without tools.
• Box contents: RMX3260 jigsaw, 20V 4Ah USB-C battery with cable, 4 blades (100 x 1.5 x 45 mm), vacuum connector, cutting limiter.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>37000RMX25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX370 – 20V Brushless Cordless Electric Pruning Shears, Ø 37 mm Cut, without
        Battery or Charger</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/foarfeca-gradina-ruris-rmx370-803</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/foarfeca-gradina-ruris-rmx370-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-803_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/foarfeca-gradina-ruris-rmx370-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-803_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>130.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>37000RMX25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003017</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX370 cordless electric pruning shears trim fruit trees, vines and shrubs effortlessly. Their 840 W brushless motor cuts branches up to 37 mm in diameter in 0.4 seconds, with quiet, long-lasting operation. Light and easy to handle, they come with a carrying case, Allen key, flat spanner and oil bottle. Sold without battery or charger, compatible with RURIS 20V batteries.

• Powerful cutting: 840 W brushless motor slicing through branches up to 37 mm in diameter, even in hardwoods.
• Fast and clean: 0.4-second cutting time per branch to prune fruit trees, vines and shrubs without fatigue.
• Maintenance-free brushless motor: low wear, quiet operation and extended service life, season after season.
• Light and ergonomic: around 1.6 kg, easy to handle and carry in its rugged case to work across the whole plot.
• Sold without battery or charger: supplied with case, Allen key, flat spanner and lubricating oil bottle; works with RURIS 20V batteries.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12150frp25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1215 – 15 m 1/2" Porous Soaker Hose, Drip Irrigation, 4-6 L/min Flow, UV-Resistant</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-poros-ruris-1215-738</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-poros-ruris-1215-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-738.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/8129FWlhO9L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>18.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12150frp25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003208</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1215 porous soaker hose releases water slowly and evenly along its 15 metres, directly at root level, for deep hydration of flower beds, vegetable gardens and shrubs. It saves up to 70% water compared with conventional watering, with an adjustable flow of 4 to 6 L/min. Made of UV-resistant rubber certified food-safe, it can be laid on the surface or buried up to 20 cm. Supplied with connectors and a tap adapter.

• Efficient irrigation: slow, even water distribution at the base of plants over 15 m, for deep root hydration without wetting the foliage.
• Up to 70% water savings: the porous rubber structure greatly reduces evaporation compared with conventional watering, with an adjustable flow of 4 to 6 L/min.
• Standard 1/2 inch format: 12.4 mm inner and 17 mm outer diameter, compatible with most irrigation systems; lay on the surface or bury up to 20 cm.
• Durable and safe: rubber with a 2.3 mm wall and UV protection, certified food-safe, ideal for vegetable gardens and aromatic herbs.
• Box contents: 15 m porous hose, connector with control valve and tap adapter, and connector with stop plug.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12200hyb25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Hybrid1220 – 30 m Garden Hose, 1/2 Inch, 3-Layer Polyfusion, 35 Bar, Anti-Twist</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-ruris-hybrid1220-739</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-hybrid1220-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-739.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-hybrid1220-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-739_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>25.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12200hyb25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003161</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The 30 m RURIS Hybrid1220 garden hose is made using 3-layer Polyfusion technology, for pressure resistance up to 35 bar. Compatible with 1/2 inch fittings, it features UV protection and an anti-twist system that prevents kinks while watering. A durable choice for daily watering of lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens.

• High-pressure resistant: 3-layer Polyfusion construction withstanding up to 35 bar, for a garden hose that lasts even under intensive use.
• 30 m length in 1/2 inch format: covers the whole garden and connects to standard 1/2" connectors, spray guns and sprinklers.
• Anti-twist system: the hose does not kink or tangle, for a constant water flow while watering.
• UV protection: material treated against sunlight, keeping its flexibility and strength season after season.
• Box contents: 30 m Hybrid1220 garden hose, ready to fit your watering system.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12300hyb25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Hybrid1230 – 30 m 1/2" Garden Hose, 3-Layer Polyfusion, 35 Bar, Anti-Twist,
        UV-Resistant</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-ruris-hybrid1230-740</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-hybrid1230-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-740.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81M7XE2EiAL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>32.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12300hyb25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003178</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The 30-metre RURIS Hybrid1230 garden hose combines a 3-layer hybrid polymer with a polyester reinforcement thanks to Polyfusion technology. Flexible, anti-twist and anti-knot, it unrolls easily even in tight spaces. It withstands 35 bar of pressure, UV rays, algae and temperatures from -10 to +60 °C, and is certified food-safe. Supplied with 2 quick connectors and a tap adapter.

• Polyfusion technology: 3 layers of hybrid polymer bonded with polyester reinforcement for a flexible, anti-twist, anti-knot hose.
• Highly resistant: 35 bar burst pressure, 2.7 mm wall and operating range from -10 to +60 °C to last season after season.
• 30 m format in 1/2 inch: 12 mm inner and 17.4 mm outer diameter, compatible with most taps, fittings and watering accessories.
• Safe and durable: UV protection, algae resistance and food-safe certification, suitable for vegetable gardens and aromatic herbs.
• Box contents: 30 m hose, 2 quick connectors and 1 tap adapter for immediate, tool-free installation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12205frf25a</id>
      <name>RURIS NTS1220-5 – 20 m 1/2" Garden Hose, 5-Layer Anti-Twist NTS, UV-Resistant</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-ruris-hybrid1220-739</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-nts1220-5-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-741.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>24.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12205frf25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003185</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The 20-metre RURIS NTS1220-5 garden hose ensures steady, convenient watering of the garden. Its 5-layer structure with NTS (No Torsion System) anti-twist technology prevents twists and knots for a constant water flow, even around flower beds and through narrow passages. UV-resistant and compatible with standard 1/2 inch fittings, it is a lasting companion for watering both the lawn and the vegetable garden.

• NTS anti-twist: the No Torsion System prevents twists and knots for a constant water flow along the entire length of the hose.
• Practical length: 20 metres in the standard 1/2 inch format, suited to small and medium-sized gardens.
• 5-layer structure: reinforced construction offering good resistance to pressure and everyday wear.
• UV-resistant: designed for outdoor use, it stays flexible and durable season after season.
• Compatible: connects to standard 1/2 inch taps, quick connectors and watering accessories.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12305frf25a</id>
      <name>RURIS NTS1230-5 – 30 m 1/2" Garden Hose, 5-Layer Anti-Twist NTS, 30 Bar, 2 Connectors
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-ruris-nts1230-5-742</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-nts1230-5-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-742.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-ruris-nts1230-5-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-742_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>32.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12305frf25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003192</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The 30-metre RURIS NTS1230-5 garden hose ensures steady, comfortable watering of the garden. Its NTS (No Torsion System) technology prevents twists and knots for a constant flow, even in gardens with complex layouts. Its polyester-reinforced 5-layer structure, resistant to UV and to 30 bar of pressure, guarantees a long service life. Supplied with 2 quick connectors and a tap adapter.

• NTS anti-twist: the No Torsion System prevents twists and knots for a constant water flow along the entire length.
• Wide coverage: 30 metres of hose in the standard 1/2 inch format, compatible with most watering fittings and accessories.
• 5-layer structure: polyester-reinforced and resistant to pressures up to 30 bar for excellent longevity.
• UV-resistant: designed for outdoor use, it stays flexible and durable season after season.
• Box contents: 30 m hose, 2 quick connectors and a tap adapter for immediate setup.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12150prs25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1215PC – 15 m 1/2" Flat Textile Soaker Hose, Oxford 210D, 9-10 L/min, Connectors
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/furtun-textil-poros-ruris-1215pc-817</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/furtun-textil-poros-ruris-1215pc-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-817_2.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81YqGIL+-gL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>27.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12150prs25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003154</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1215PC flat textile soaker hose distributes water evenly along its 15 metres, directly at the plants' roots, and saves up to 80% water compared with conventional watering. Made of Oxford 210D fabric with PVC, PP and ABS, it delivers 9 to 10 L/min at 4 bar and connects to 1/2 inch systems. Flat, light (0.708 kg) and easy to store, it comes with one connector and one connector with water stop.

• Root-level irrigation: flat, porous design distributing water evenly over 15 m, with up to 80% water savings compared with conventional watering.
• Rugged textile: Oxford 210D fabric combined with PVC, PP and ABS to withstand wear and outdoor conditions all season long.
• Steady flow: 9 to 10 L/min at 4 bar of pressure, compatible with standard 1/2 inch watering systems; operating temperature from 5 to 35 °C.
• Compact and light: flat 0.708 kg format that folds and stores without taking up space, ideal for small and medium-sized gardens.
• Box contents: 15 m flat soaker hose, 1/2 inch connector and 1/2 inch connector with water stop for tool-free assembly.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20000RUR25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS R-Power IS2000 – 2000 W Petrol Inverter Generator, Quiet, THD &lt; 3%, 4 L Tank</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/generatoare-de-curent/generator-invertor-ruris-is2000-714</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/generator-invertor-ruris-is2000-pds-44-1920-1024-0-0-714.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/generator-invertor-ruris-is2000-pds-44-1920-1024-0-0-714_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Generators</category>
      <price_with_vat>499.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20000RUR25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739061796</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS R-Power IS2000 inverter generator is a portable, quiet and reliable power source to run your appliances during power outages, while camping or outdoors. Its 3 HP 4-stroke engine delivers 2000 W through a 230 V socket, with low distortion (THD < 3%) that protects sensitive electronics. 4 L tank for up to 5.7 hours of runtime at 50% load.

• 2000 W of power: 3 HP 4-stroke engine sufficient to run lighting, TV, computer, booster pump and other appliances via a 230 V socket.
• Quiet inverter technology: discreet operation, ideal for camping, urban areas or extended power outages.
• Clean, stable power: automatic voltage regulator and low harmonic distortion (THD < 3%) to protect your sensitive electronic devices.
• Long runtime: up to 5.7 hours of operation at 50% load thanks to the 4 L fuel tank.
• Portable and practical: compact 19.8 kg format, easy to move around as a backup power source at home or outdoors.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1008s2021am</id>
      <name>RURIS AquaPower 1008S – 750W Booster Pump, 19L Tank, 46 L/min Flow, 45 m Head, Pressure
        Gauge</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofoare/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-1008s-158</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-1008s-pds-58-1920-1024-0-0-158.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Booster Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>99.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1008s2021am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000252</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AquaPower 1008S booster pump (750W) automatically supplies the house and garden with water from a well, cistern or rainwater tank. With its 46 L/min flow rate, 45 m delivery head and 19 L anti-corrosion tank, it ensures constant pressure for sanitary fittings, washing machines and watering. Cast-iron pump body and bronze impeller for a long service life.

• Efficient pumping: 750 W motor delivering a 46 L/min flow rate, a 45 m delivery head and suction down to 9 m for a reliable water supply.
• Versatile uses: supplies toilets, washbasins, washing machines, watering or cleaning systems, using well or rainwater to save drinking water.
• 19 L anti-corrosion tank: the stored pressure reduces pump start-ups, for optimised power consumption and less motor wear.
• Durable construction: cast-iron pump body and bronze impeller for maximum resistance and a long service life, even in regular use.
• Easy installation: convenient side switch, wide filling opening, built-in pressure gauge and perforated feet for stable floor mounting.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2010s2021am</id>
      <name>RURIS AquaPower 2010S – 900W Booster Pump, 24L Tank, 52 L/min Flow, 50 m Head, Pressure
        Gauge</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofoare/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-2010s-159</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-2010s-pds-58-1920-1024-0-0-159.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Booster Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>129.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2010s2021am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000269</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AquaPower 2010S booster pump (900W) automatically distributes water throughout the house and garden from a well or a rainwater collection tank. Its 52 L/min flow rate, 50 m delivery head and 24 L anti-corrosion tank guarantee constant pressure for sanitary fittings, washing machines and watering. Cast-iron body, stainless steel impeller and flexible hose included.

• Powerful, automatic pumping: 900 W motor, 52 L/min flow rate and delivery head up to 50 m to distribute water efficiently throughout the house.
• Versatile uses: ideal for washbasins, toilets, washing machines, watering and cleaning systems, with suction down to 9 m from wells or cisterns.
• 24 L anti-corrosion tank: the stored pressure limits frequent pump restarts, for constant pressure and reduced power consumption.
• Robust design: cast-iron pump body, stainless steel impeller and stable feet with mounting holes for a durable, vibration-free installation.
• Economical and eco-friendly: makes use of rainwater or well water to cut drinking water consumption and household costs; flexible hose included.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2011s2021am</id>
      <name>RURIS AquaPower 2011S – 1100W Booster Pump, 50 L Tank, 58 L/min Flow, 55 m Head</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofoare/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-2011s-165</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofor-ruris-aquapower-2011s-pds-58-1920-1024-0-0-165.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Booster Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>159.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2011s2021am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000276</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS AquaPower 2011S booster pump (1100W) provides an automatic, constant water supply for the whole house, even under intensive use. It delivers a 58 L/min flow rate, a 55 m delivery head, suction down to 9 m and a large 50 L anti-corrosion tank that limits pump restarts. Ideal for using well or rainwater for sanitary fittings, watering and cleaning.

• High performance: 1100 W motor, 58 L/min flow rate, suction down to 9 m and a 55 m delivery head for reliable, intensive household use.
• Large 50 L tank: anti-corrosion vessel that stores pressure and prevents frequent pump restarts, for greater comfort and longevity.
• Versatile uses: supplies sanitary fittings and the washing machine, waters the garden, cleans the terrace or washes vehicles from a well or cistern.
• Economical and eco-friendly: allows the use of rainwater or well water, reducing drinking water consumption and household energy costs.
• Easy installation and maintenance: sturdy cast-iron pump, built-in pressure gauge, side switch, feet with mounting holes and easy draining for winter storage.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>62000SLH25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS Smart Light High Pressure 62 – 1150W Booster Pump, 62 L/min, 50 m Head, Digital
        Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofoare/hidrofor-ruris-smart-light-high-pressure-62-768</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofor-ruris-smart-light-high-pressure-62-pds-58-1920-1024-0-0-768.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Booster Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>249.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>62000SLH25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739063356</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Smart Light High Pressure 62 booster pump (1150W) delivers a flow rate of 62 L/min and a delivery head of 50 m, supplying several water points at once without any drop in pressure. Its suction depth of up to 9 m makes it suitable for wells, cisterns and tanks. Rust-proof cast iron body, bronze impeller, digital display, automatic start/stop and dry-run and overload protections.

• Flow rate of 62 L/min and 50 m delivery head: simultaneously supplies the bathroom, kitchen, washing machine and garden watering without pressure loss, even across several floors.
• Suction up to 9 m: efficiently draws water from wells, cisterns, tanks or low-pressure networks, for maximum compatibility with your installation.
• Premium construction: rust-treated cast iron body, bronze impeller and copper winding on the 1150 W motor for lasting performance under intensive use.
• Smart functions and safety: digital monitoring display, Start-Up Delay, dry-run protection and overload protection for safe everyday operation.
• Automatic and manual start/stop: the pump activates according to actual water demand, avoiding unnecessary running and reducing power consumption.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>90000SMH25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS Smart Magnetic High Pressure 90 – 1150W Inverter Booster Pump, 90 L/min, 50 m,
        Digital Display</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofoare/hidrofor-rurissmart-magnetic-high-pressure-90-769</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/hidrofor-rurissmart-magnetic-high-pressure-90-pds-58-1920-1024-0-0-769.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Booster Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>329.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>90000SMH25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003437</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Smart Magnetic High Pressure 90 booster pump (1150W) delivers a flow rate of 90 L/min and a delivery head of 50 m for demanding household use. Its permanent-magnet inverter adjusts motor speed to actual water demand, saving energy and running quietly. Digital display with pressure adjustment and timer, rust-proof cast iron body, IPX4 protection. Weight: 6.5 kg.

• Flow rate of 90 L/min and 50 m delivery head: simultaneously supplies the bathroom, kitchen, washing machine and garden watering without pressure loss, even across several floors.
• Permanent-magnet inverter: motor speed (up to 5600 rpm) adapts to water demand, reducing power consumption, noise and water hammer.
• Digital display and smart functions: pressure adjustment, programmable timer, consumption tracking and error indicator for quick diagnostics.
• Durable construction: rust-treated cast iron body, PPO impeller, copper winding and IPX4 protection for safe use in damp environments.
• Suction up to 8 m: draws from wells, cisterns and tanks; max water temperature 50 °C, 2 m power cable and 6.5 kg weight for easy installation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>64000rre26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 64e Fast Charger VoltX 60V 4A 260W for ALFA UP 6400e and 6800e Batteries, LED
        Diagnostics</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/incarcator-ruris-64e-859</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/incarcator-ruris-64e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-859_6.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery Tool Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>64000rre26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020588</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 64e is the fast charger dedicated to the VoltX 60V platform: with 4A output current and 260W, it recharges the ALFA UP 6400e (4Ah) and 6800e (8Ah) batteries considerably faster than a standard 2A charger. Its intelligent temperature management delays charging if the battery is too hot, and the red/green LED panel shows the charge status at a glance. Not compatible with RURIS 20V batteries.

• Fast 4A 260W charging: recharges VoltX 60V batteries up to twice as fast as a standard 2A charger, reducing waiting time between work sessions.
• One charger for the whole VoltX fleet: compatible with the ALFA UP 6400e (60V 4Ah) and 6800e (60V 8Ah) batteries used on brush cutters, chainsaws, hedge trimmers and blowers.
• Intelligent temperature management: charging is automatically delayed if the battery is too hot after use, preserving the cells over the long term.
• Built-in safety: overload and short-circuit protections, double insulation and rail-mounted insertion with no adjustment needed, for worry-free unattended charging.
• Box contents: 1 RURIS 64e VoltX 60V charger with red/green LED diagnostic panel and 230 V mains cable. Not compatible with RURIS 20V batteries.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>30024rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 30024e – 300 W Portable Power Station with 4 x 20V 4Ah Batteries Included, AC
        240V, USB-C</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/invertor-portabil-ruris-30024e-873</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/invertor-portabil-ruris-30024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-873.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>244.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>30024rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033410</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 30024e is a 300 W portable inverter supplied with 4 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries included (320 Wh in total) and automatic switching between batteries with no interruption. Plugged into the mains, it recharges all 4 batteries simultaneously. AC 240V, USB-C 18W, 2x USB-A and DC 12V/5A outputs, plus a 7.2 W LED lamp: a complete mobile power solution for camping, the garden and power outages.

• Ready-to-use 300 W power station: 4 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries included (320 Wh) with automatic switching from one battery to the next without interruption.
• Inverter and quadruple charger in one: plugged into the mains, it recharges all 4 batteries simultaneously; the batteries also power all RURIS 20V tools.
• Mobile power strip: AC 210-240V, USB-C 18W fast charging, 2x USB-A 5V/2A and DC 12V/5A outputs to power several devices at once.
• Safe and practical: overcurrent, short-circuit and overheating protections; built-in 7.2 W LED lamp for emergency lighting during power cuts.
• Box contents: 30024e inverter, 4 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with LED display and bidirectional USB-C port, 4 USB-C cables and mains adapter.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>58150kit25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 5815 – Misting Kit for Terrace and Pergola, Fine Water Droplets, No Electricity
        Needed</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/kit-terase-ruris-5815-795</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/spray-kit-ruris-5815-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-795.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/spray-kit-ruris-5815-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-795_6.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>25.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>58150kit25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003482</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 5815 misting kit cools terraces, pergolas and verandas by spraying fine water droplets that lower the perceived temperature on hot days. It attaches along a structure, connects to the garden hose and runs on mains water pressure, with no electricity required. Ideal for dining areas, restaurant terraces and outdoor relaxation spaces.

• Effective cooling: sprays fine water droplets that lower the perceived temperature on the terrace during hot summer days.
• Versatile: suitable for terraces, pergolas, verandas and dining areas, creating a pleasant outdoor space all summer long.
• Works without electricity: simply uses mains water pressure via the garden hose, with nozzles ensuring an even spray.
• Easy installation: attaches along a pergola or awning and connects to the garden hose, with quick tool-free assembly.
• Light and discreet: compact set of around 0.87 kg, easy to install at the start of the season and to store away afterwards.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>13900RMX26B</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1390 – Cordless Brushless Drill Driver 130 Nm, 2 Speeds, 20V 4Ah Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-multifunctionala-ruris-rmx1390-599</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-multifunctional-drill-ruris-rmx1390-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-599.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-multifunctional-drill-ruris-rmx1390-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-599_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>13900RMX26B</mpn>
      <ean>5940739064384</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1390 cordless drill driver with brushless motor delivers 130 Nm of torque with 2 mechanical speeds (0-300 and 0-1200 rpm) to drill wood up to 150 mm and metal up to 13 mm. 3-16 mm chuck, LED light and 3-position handle. Supplied with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with USB-C charging (cable included, no mains charger), an 80x300 mm earth auger bit and 9 wood/metal drill bits.

• High 130 Nm torque: brushless motor and 2 mechanical speeds (0-300 and 0-1200 rpm) to drill wood up to 150 mm and metal up to 13 mm.
• 20V 4Ah battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e battery with bidirectional USB-C charging, rechargeable from any USB-C port and usable as a power bank for your mobile devices.
• Versatile 3-16 mm chuck: compatible with a wide range of drill bits, with a 3-position D-handle and 150 mm extension for safe guidance.
• Ideal for heavy jobs: pilot holes in beams, fence posts and planting supports thanks to the included 80x300 mm earth auger bit, with LED lighting.
• Box contents: RMX1390 drill, 20V 4Ah USB-C battery with cable, 80x300 mm earth auger bit, 5 metal drill bits, 4 wood drill bits, chuck key, adapter, D-handle.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1360rma2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1360 – Cordless Brushless Hammer Drill Driver 60 Nm, Battery and Charger
        Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-cu-percutie-ruris-rmx1360-598</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-drillscrewdriver-ruris-rmx1360-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-598.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-drillscrewdriver-ruris-rmx1360-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-598_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>79.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1360rma2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003574</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1360 cordless hammer drill driver combines a brushless motor, 2 speeds (0-450 and 0-2000 rpm), 60 Nm of torque and a hammer action of 30,000 blows/min to drill wood, metal, concrete and masonry. 0-13 mm keyless chuck and LED lighting. 20V 2Ah battery and charger included, along with 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm) so you can start right away.

• Long-lasting brushless motor: constant power and extended service life for drilling and driving in wood, metal and masonry.
• 2 selectable speeds: 0-450 rpm for high torque and precise screwdriving, 0-2000 rpm for fast, efficient drilling.
• 30,000 blows/min hammer action: penetrates concrete and masonry with no extra effort, with a 0-13 mm keyless chuck and 60 Nm of torque.
• Built-in LED: optimal visibility in dark corners so you can work precisely in any situation.
• Battery and charger included: supplied with a 20V 2Ah lithium battery, charger, 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm), ready to use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1260rma2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1260 – Cordless Brushless Drill Driver 60 Nm, 2 Speeds, Battery and Charger
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1260-597</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx1260-cordless-drill-screwdriver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-597.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx1260-cordless-drill-screwdriver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-597_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>72.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1260rma2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003598</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1260 cordless drill driver relies on a brushless motor, 2 speeds (0-450 and 0-2000 rpm) and 60 Nm of torque to drill and drive in wood, metal and plastic. 0-10 mm keyless chuck, built-in LED and charge indicator. 20V 2Ah battery and charger included, with 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm) so you can work straight out of the box.

• Efficient brushless motor: greater efficiency, reduced wear and constant power for all your drilling and screwdriving jobs.
• 2 versatile speeds: 0-450 rpm for high torque and controlled screwdriving, 0-2000 rpm for fast drilling in soft materials.
• 60 Nm torque and 0-10 mm chuck: great flexibility for driving and drilling with a wide range of drill bits and screwdriver bits.
• User comfort: built-in LED for dark areas and battery level indicator to keep track of remaining runtime.
• Battery and charger included: supplied with a 20V 2Ah lithium battery, charger, 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm), ready to use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1240rma2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1240 – Cordless Brushless Drill Driver 20V, 21 Torque Settings, Battery and
        Charger Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-596</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-596.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-596_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>65.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1240rma2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739061727</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1240 cordless drill driver is light (0.94 kg) and versatile: 20V brushless motor, 2 speeds (0-400 and 0-1350 rpm), 21 torque settings and a 0-10 mm chuck. It drills up to 25 mm in wood and 10 mm in metal, with built-in LED lighting. 20V 2Ah battery and charger included, plus 8 bits, 8 drill bits (2-6 mm), magnetic adapter and countersink bit.

• 20V brushless motor: high energy efficiency, constant power and reduced maintenance for a long service life.
• 2 speeds and 21 torque settings: 0-400 rpm for precise screwdriving, 0-1350 rpm for fast drilling, without damaging screws or materials.
• Versatile capacities: 0-10 mm chuck, drilling up to 25 mm in wood and 10 mm in metal, driving screws up to 10 mm in diameter.
• Light and precise: only 0.94 kg with built-in LED lighting, comfortable even in awkward positions or during long work sessions.
• Battery and charger included: complete kit with 20V 2Ah battery, 8 bits, 8 drill bits (2-6 mm), magnetic adapter and countersink bit, ready to use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>23000rmx26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX2300 – Cordless Impact Driver 20V 230 Nm, 3300 rpm, 1/4" Hex, 4Ah Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-insurubat-cu-impact-ruris-rmx2300-600</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-impact-driver-ruris-rmx2300-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-600.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-impact-driver-ruris-rmx2300-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-600_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>85.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>23000rmx26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033342</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX2300 cordless impact driver with brushless motor delivers 230 Nm, 3300 rpm and 4500 blows/min to drive and remove M8 to M18 screws effortlessly. Ultra-compact (0.94 kg), it suits tradespeople, electricians and carpenters. Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging and cable, ready to use straight out of the box.

• 230 Nm torque and brushless motor: 3300 rpm and 4500 blows/min to drive bolts and long M8-M18 screws where a standard drill driver stalls.
• Ideal for assembly, construction and mechanics: ultra-compact 0.94 kg format for reaching tight spaces and handling repetitive screwdriving.
• 1/4 inch (6.35 mm) hex socket: quick bit changes; torque adjustable in 3 stages and Reversal Stop function to avoid damaging screws and soft materials.
• Comfort and control: LED lighting, battery level indicator and balanced grip for precise work even in dark areas.
• Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C port and cable; recharges from any USB-C port and also powers your other RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>35000rmx26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3500 – Cordless Impact Wrench 20V 350 Nm, 1/2" Square Drive, 3300 bpm, 4Ah
        Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-insurubat-cu-impact-ruris-rmx3500-601</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx3500-cordless-impact-driver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-601.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx3500-cordless-impact-driver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-601_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>83.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>35000rmx26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033366</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3500 cordless impact wrench with brushless motor develops an extreme torque of 350 Nm, 2400 rpm and 3300 blows/min for heavy bolting: car wheels, rusted nuts, M8-M18 fasteners. Its 1/2 inch square drive accepts standard impact sockets. Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging and cable.

• Extreme 350 Nm torque: brushless motor at 2400 rpm and 3300 blows/min to tighten and loosen large bolts up to M18 effortlessly.
• Ideal for automotive mechanics and construction: removes wheels, rusted nuts and seized fasteners, for garage mechanics and building professionals.
• 1/2 inch square drive: compatible with standard impact sockets; torque adjustable in 3 stages and Reversal Stop function for precise tightening control.
• Compact and comfortable: only 1 kg, with LED lighting and battery level indicator for efficient work anywhere.
• Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C port and cable; recharges from any USB-C port and also powers your other RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>11000dac26a</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 110XR – Self-Propelled Petrol Lawn Mower 3.3 HP 131 cc, 41 cm Cutting Width,
        45 L Bag, up to 400 m²</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-882</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-882.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-882_12.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>216.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>11000dac26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020274</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The DAC 110XR self-propelled petrol lawn mower is fitted with a 131 cc Ducar 4-stroke engine (3.3 HP) with electronic ignition. Its 41 cm cutting width and 45 L grass collection bag make it the ideal solution for residential gardens of 200 to 400 m². The all-metal deck ensures durability, the cutting height adjusts from 25 to 75 mm across 7 positions, and rear discharge complements the collection function. Fuel consumption: 0.7 L/h.

• Proven Ducar engine: 131 cc 4-stroke engine developing 3.3 HP, with electronic ignition and moderate fuel consumption of 0.7 L/h.
• Effortless self-propulsion: the self-drive system reduces fatigue and makes regular mowing of residential gardens of 200 to 400 m² easier.
• All-metal deck: fully metal construction that is far more resistant to impacts and wear than the plastic decks in the same segment.
• Precisely adjustable cutting: height from 25 to 75 mm across 7 positions, 41 cm cutting width, with collection and rear discharge functions to choose from.
• Everyday comfort: 45 L collection bag to space out emptying, 7-inch front wheels and 8-inch rear wheels for good stability.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12000dac26a</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 120XR – Self-Propelled Petrol Lawn Mower 4 HP 150 cc, 46 cm, 5 Functions with
        Mulching, 55 L Bag</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-883</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-883.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-883.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>255.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12000dac26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020281</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The DAC 120XR self-propelled petrol lawn mower features a 150 cc Ducar 4-stroke engine (4 HP) with a throttle variator to match power to grass density. Its 46 cm cutting width and 55 L bag suit gardens of 300 to 600 m². It offers 5 functions: collection, rear discharge, side discharge, mulching and deck washing. Metal deck, cutting height adjustable from 25 to 75 mm across 8 positions.

• Ducar engine with variator: 150 cc 4-stroke (4 HP) with a throttle variator to adjust power to the grass and save fuel (0.8 L/h).
• 5 versatile functions: collection in the 55 L bag, rear discharge, side discharge, fertilising mulching and deck-wash function via water connector.
• Self-propelled for medium to large areas: self-drive and the 46 cm width reduce effort and the number of passes over 300 to 600 m².
• Fine cutting adjustment: height adjustable from 25 to 75 mm across 8 positions, to suit the season and keep the lawn healthy.
• Durable construction: tough metal deck, 7-inch front wheels and 8-inch rear wheels for stable mowing on uneven ground.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1200rxe2023am</id>
      <name>RURIS RXE1200 – Electric Lawn Mower 1200 W, 32 cm Cutting Width, 3 Heights 25-60 mm, 30
        L Bag</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-electrica-ruris-rxe1200-558</link>
      <image>http://feed.ruris.ro/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/RURIS-RXE1200-detaliu-01.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>66.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1200rxe2023am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000580</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXE1200 electric lawn mower keeps residential lawns in shape reliably. Its 1200 W motor running at 3100 rpm and 32 cm cutting width deliver a clean cut, even in dense grass. Three cutting heights (25, 45 and 60 mm) adapt to every season, while the 30 L grass collection bag reduces interruptions. Its folding handle makes storage and transport easy.

• 1200 W motor: runs at 3100 rpm to tackle the dense grass of residential gardens, with consistent performance and instant start-up.
• Clean, quiet mowing: mains-powered, it runs without fuel, emissions or a pull cord, and requires no engine maintenance.
• Cutting height adjustable to 3 levels: 25, 45 or 60 mm to match the mowing to the season and your preferences, over a 32 cm working width.
• 30 L collection bag: generous capacity that reduces trips to empty the grass and allows continuous, tidy work.
• Compact and light: folding handle and a weight of around 9.4 kg for easy storage and effortless transport, ideal for small gardens.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>14000rxe26a</id>
      <name>RURIS RXE1400 Confort – Electric Lawn Mower 1400 W, 34 cm Cutting Width, 6 Heights 20-70
        mm, 35 L Bag</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/main-de-tuns-gazon-electrica-886</link>
      <image>
        https://m.media-amazon.com/images/S/al-eu-726f4d26-7fdb/5f55263f-a2be-4f53-89f9-4dd60aa644f7.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/816qhlAnf8L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>100.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>14000rxe26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020359</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXE1400 Confort electric lawn mower cares for residential lawns with precision. Its 1400 W motor at 3500 rpm cuts over a 34 cm width, with 6 heights from 20 to 70 mm set via a single central adjustment. Its grass comb lifts flattened blades before cutting for a uniform finish, and its 35 L bag with fill-level indicator reduces stops. Adjustable and foldable Confort Pro handle.

• 1400 W motor at 3500 rpm: constant power for a clean, even cut on residential lawns, with instant start-up on 230 V mains.
• 6 cutting heights from 20 to 70 mm: a single central adjustment sets all 4 wheels in one movement, with a visual indicator of the selected level.
• Grass-lifting comb: positioned in front of the blade, it raises flattened blades before cutting for an even result, even on uneven lawns.
• Confort Pro handle: ergonomic, height-adjustable to suit the user and foldable for compact storage in the garage or shed.
• 35 L collection bag: fill-level indicator so you empty it at the right time, with optional rear discharge to leave clippings on the ground; only 9 kg.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1500rxe2023am</id>
      <name>RURIS RXE1500 – Electric Lawn Mower 1500 W, 37 cm Cutting Width, 25-75 mm Cutting
        Height, 35 L Grass Box</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-electrica-ruris-rxe1500-570</link>
      <image>http://feed.ruris.ro/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/MASINA-TUNS-GAZON-RURIS-RXE1500-detalii-1.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>104.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1500rxe2023am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739003840</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXE1500 electric lawn mower combines power and comfort for maintaining residential lawns. Its 1500 W motor running at 3300 rpm cuts thick grass efficiently over a 37 cm width, with a cutting height adjustable from 25 to 75 mm. The 35 L grass collection box reduces interruptions, and the foldable handle makes storage easy, even in tight spaces.

• 1500 W motor: runs at 3300 rpm to cut thick grass and handle uneven terrain, with instant start-up and no pull cord.
• 37 cm cutting width: covers medium-sized lawns quickly, for efficient mowing of urban and residential gardens.
• Adjustable cutting height from 25 to 75 mm: three levels to adapt mowing to the season, grass type and your maintenance preferences.
• Quiet and clean: 230 V mains power, no fuel, no emissions and no engine maintenance, considerate to your neighbours.
• 35 L grass box and foldable handle: large collection capacity that reduces stops, plus compact storage made easy for the garage or garden shed.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>18000rxe26a</id>
      <name>RURIS RXE1800 Confort – Electric Lawn Mower 1800 W, 40 cm Cutting Width, 3-in-1
        Mulching, 40 L Grass Box</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-electrica-881</link>
      <image>
        http://feed.ruris.ro/wp-content/uploads/2026/05/RURIS-RXE1800-Confort_detaliu_1.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>140.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>18000rxe26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020366</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXE1800 Confort electric lawn mower tackles even the densest lawns. Its 1800 W motor running at 3500 rpm cuts across a 40 cm width, with 7 cutting heights from 25 to 75 mm set via central adjustment. Choose from three functions: collection in the 40 L box, rear discharge or fertilising mulching. The foam Confort Pro handle is adjustable and foldable, and vertical storage keeps the footprint to a minimum.

• 1800 W motor at 3500 rpm: mows even thick, dense lawns efficiently without losing power, over a 40 cm cutting width.
• 3 functions in 1: collection in the box, rear discharge, or mulching that finely chops the grass and returns it to the lawn as natural fertiliser.
• 7 cutting heights from 25 to 75 mm: central adjustment button sets all 4 wheels with a single press, with a visual indicator of the selected level.
• Comfort and storage: anti-vibration foam Confort Pro handle, height-adjustable and foldable; vertical storage for a minimal footprint.
• 40 L collection box: large capacity with a fill-level indicator to avoid clogging and interruptions; net weight of 12 kg for easy everyday handling.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>37440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RXI3744e – Cordless Lawn Mower 2x20V, 37 cm Cutting Width, 3-in-1, 2x 4Ah
        Batteries Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rxi3744e-557</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-3324e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-565.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91BmNWF-NmL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>170.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>37440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034745</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXI3744e cordless lawn mower pairs a 2x20V brushless motor (40V, 160 Wh) with a 37 cm cutting width to maintain lawns of up to 650 m². Cutting height is adjustable from 25 to 75 mm, and the 3-in-1 function offers collection in the 35 L bag, rear discharge or mulching. Lightweight (13 kg) and quiet, it comes with 2 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with USB-C charging.

• 40V power: brushless motor powered by 2x 20V 4Ah batteries (160 Wh) and a 37 cm cutting width for gardens up to 650 m².
• 3-in-1 function: collection in the 35 L bag, rear discharge, or mulching to redistribute the finely cut grass over the lawn.
• Adjustable cut: cutting height from 25 to 75 mm, with 15 cm front and 20 cm rear wheels for easy manoeuvring around flower beds.
• Quiet in residential areas: mows without noise nuisance, fuel or exhaust fumes, with a contained weight of 13 kg.
• 2 batteries included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>43440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RXI4344e – Cordless Lawn Mower 2x20V, 43 cm Cutting Width, 3-in-1, 2x 4Ah
        Batteries Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rxi4344e-566</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rxi4344e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-566.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rxi4344e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-566_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>228.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>43440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034769</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXI4344e cordless lawn mower runs on 2x 20V 4Ah batteries (40V) and offers a 43 cm cutting width for gardens of 400 to 650 m². Cutting height adjusts from 25 to 75 mm across 6 positions, with a 3-in-1 function (collection, rear discharge, mulching) and a large 50 L grass bag. Its large 25 cm rear wheels make mowing easier on uneven ground. 2 ALFA UP 2400e batteries included, with USB-C charging.

• Wide cutting width: 43 cm on 2x20V power (160 Wh) to cover more ground with every pass, for lawns up to 650 m².
• 3-in-1 function: collection in the 50 L bag, rear discharge or mulching, depending on the season and the condition of the lawn.
• 6-position cutting height: adjustment from 25 to 75 mm for a finish suited to every type of grass.
• Stable on uneven terrain: large 25 cm rear wheels and 17.5 cm front wheels for better traction, with a weight of 13.5 kg.
• 2 batteries included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>200s2019am</id>
      <name>RURIS RX200S – Petrol Lawn Mower 2.7 HP, 42 cm Cutting Width, 45 L Grass Box, 3-in-1
        Mulching, up to 1300 m²</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rx200s-310</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71qaC+a0YqL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81+67N8F7TL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>189.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>200s2019am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739004014</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RX200S petrol lawn mower maintains lawns of up to 1300 m² with no cable to hold you back. Its 2.7 HP 4-stroke engine drives a 42 cm blade, with 3 functions: collection in a 45 L box, rear discharge and mulching to fertilise the lawn. Cutting height adjusts from 25 to 75 mm over 5 positions, and the pressed steel chassis ensures a long service life. Foldable handlebar and grass box for compact storage.

• High-performance petrol engine: 2.7 HP 4-stroke engine and 42 cm cutting width to mow lawns up to 1300 m² efficiently, with no power cable.
• 3-in-1 versatility: collection in the 45 L box, rear discharge, or mulching that finely shreds the grass and naturally fertilises the lawn.
• Adjustable cutting height: 5 positions from 25 to 75 mm to adapt mowing to the season, grass type and desired result.
• Durable construction: pressed steel chassis resistant to impacts and wear, built for regular use season after season.
• Easy transport and storage: ergonomic handle, foldable handlebar and grass box for compact storage in the garden shed or garage.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>221s2019am</id>
      <name>RURIS RX221S – Petrol Lawn Mower 3.5 HP, 42 cm Cutting Width, 45 L Grass Box, 3-in-1
        Mulching, up to 1500 m²</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/masina-de-tuns-gazon-ruris-rx221s-311</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71mFrmP9ysL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81SoqbobWtL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>239.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>221s2019am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739004021</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RX221S petrol lawn mower is designed for lawns of up to 1500 m². Its 3.5 HP 4-stroke engine and 42 cm cutting width ensure fast mowing, with 3 modes to choose from: collection in the 45 L box, rear discharge or mulching. The pressed steel chassis and four wheels deliver strength and manoeuvrability, while cutting height adjusts from 25 to 75 mm over 5 positions. Foldable handlebar and grass box.

• Power and efficiency: 3.5 HP 4-stroke engine paired with a 42 cm cutting width to maintain lawns of up to 1500 m² effortlessly.
• 3-in-1 versatility: collection in the 45 L box, rear discharge, or mulching to naturally feed the lawn with finely shredded grass.
• Tailored cut: cutting height adjustable from 25 to 75 mm in 5 positions, for a lawn suited to the season and your preferences.
• Strength and manoeuvrability: pressed steel chassis, adjustable ergonomic handlebar and four wheels for stable handling on uneven terrain.
• Easy storage: foldable handlebar and grass box save space in storage and make transport simple, with no cable restrictions.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>mec2014am</id>
      <name>RURIS Gospodar A1 – Hammer Grain Mill 2700 W, 180 kg/h, 4 Sieves 2-5 mm, 50 L Bag</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/mori-si-batoze/moara-ruris-gospodar-a1-76</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/moara-ruris-gospodar-a1-pds-50-1920-1024-0-0-76_5.jpg</image>
      <category>Agriculture &gt; Grain Mills</category>
      <price_with_vat>112.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>mec2014am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739004144</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Gospodar A1 hammer grain mill grinds maize, wheat and barley at up to 180 kg/h thanks to its 2700 W electric motor (220 V, 2850 rpm) with direct drive. Its 20 hammers, 2 knives and 4 interchangeable sieves from 2 to 5 mm let you choose the grind, from coarse grain to fine flour. The exclusive RURIS Anti-Reflux system reduces material loss by up to 98%; 50 L collection bag included.

• Powerful motor: 2700 W at 220 V running at 2850 rpm with direct drive, for a grinding capacity of up to 180 kg/h of grain.
• Your choice of grind: 4 interchangeable sieves from 2 to 5 mm to obtain coarse grain or fine flour, depending on use (animal feed or consumption).
• RURIS Anti-Reflux system: unground grain is returned to the processing chamber, reducing material loss by up to 98%.
• Controlled feeding: two channels (side for small volumes, top for large volumes) and a flow adjustment rod for consistent output.
• Ready to use: 20 hammers, 2 knives, 50 L collection bag and built-in on/off switch; workbench mounting, 18.8 kg with accessories.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>38640rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS VoltX 3864e – 60V Brushless Brush Cutter, 420 mm Cutting Width, 4Ah Battery and
        Charger Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motocoasa-ruris-voltx-3864e-860</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/motocoasa-ruris-voltx-3864e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-860_9.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>266.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>38640rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033489</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS VoltX 3864e cordless brush cutter combines a 60V brushless motor with direct drive (6000 rpm) and a dual cutting system: 2.4 mm line over 420 mm and a 3-tooth 350 mm blade. Ideal for maintaining plots, embankments and areas of dense vegetation, with a modular shaft and multifunction display. Supplied with an ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah battery and charger included.

• 60V brushless power: direct-drive motor running at 6000 rpm, with torque comparable to a 1.5 to 2 HP petrol engine and no loss of speed in dense vegetation.
• Versatile: dual 2.4 mm Bump Feed line head (420 mm cut) for grass and a 3-tooth blade (350 mm) for brambles and woody brush, interchangeable without tools.
• Multifunction display: battery level and speed shown in real time; modular 26 mm shaft with quick coupling for easy transport and storage.
• Extended comfort: curved Soft Grip handle with anti-vibration system and shoulder harness included to reduce fatigue during long working sessions.
• Battery and charger included: RURIS ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah (240 Wh) Li-Ion battery with digital display, compatible with all tools in the VoltX range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>30440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 3044e – 2x20V Brushless Brush Cutter, 300 mm Line, 255 mm Blade, 2 Batteries
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motocoasa-ruris-3044e-587</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/motocoasa-ruris-3044e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-587.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>155.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>30440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034738</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 3044e is a cordless brush cutter with a brushless motor powered by 2x 20V 4Ah batteries (40V, 160 Wh) for extended runtime. Its dual cutting system (300 mm line and 255 mm 3-tooth blade) handles grass and woody brush. Ideal for maintaining medium-sized areas. Supplied with 2 ALFA UP 2400e batteries with bidirectional USB-C charging and a USB-C cable.

• 2x20V (40V) power: brushless motor powered by 2x 4Ah batteries totalling 160 Wh, for longer runtime than single-battery models.
• Versatile cutting: 300 mm line head for grass and a 255 mm 3-tooth blade for woody brush, interchangeable without switching machines.
• 2 batteries included with USB-C charging: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries rechargeable from any USB-C port without a mains charger; they also serve as a power bank for your devices.
• Extended comfort: ergonomic 2-segment handles and reduced vibration for maintaining gardens, borders and dense areas without fatigue.
• Box contents: 3044e brush cutter, 2 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with LED display, USB-C cable, 300 mm line head, 255 mm 3-tooth blade, harness.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>31440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 3144e – 2x20V Brushless Brush Cutter, Modular Shaft, 300 mm Cutting Width, 2
        Batteries Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motocoasa-de-umar-pe-acumulator-ruris-3144e-872</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/motocoasa-de-umar-pe-acumulator-ruris-3144e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-872.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>152.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>31440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033434</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 3144e is a cordless brush cutter with a 2x20V (40V, 160 Wh) brushless motor running at 7500 rpm, delivering power close to entry-level petrol models with no fuel or engine maintenance. Dual cutting system: 300 mm line and 255 mm 3-tooth blade. Its modular shaft makes transport and storage easy. Supplied with 2 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with USB-C charging.

• 2x20V power (40V, 160 Wh): brushless motor at 7500 rpm that maintains high torque in thick grass, brambles and brush, with no loss of speed.
• Tool-free dual cutting: 1.6 mm Bump Feed line head (300 mm diameter) for finishing work and a 3-tooth blade (255 mm) for woody vegetation.
• Modular 26 mm shaft: splits into 2 segments to fit in a small car boot and store in a compact space.
• Working comfort: ergonomic shoulder harness, loop handle and low vibration (2.92 m/s²) for extended sessions on lawns, embankments and borders.
• 2 batteries included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah with LED display and bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank; USB-C cable supplied.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>240rr2022am</id>
      <name>RURIS RR240 BRAVO – Petrol Brush Cutter 24 cm³ 1 HP, 255 mm Cutting Width, Flexible
        Shaft, 3.8 kg</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motocoase/motocoasa-ruris-240-bravo-495</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/611M5GTZVKL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81s0BmNCBKL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Brush Cutters</category>
      <price_with_vat>159.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>240rr2022am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000832</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RR240 BRAVO petrol brush cutter maintains lawns, borders, embankments and overgrown areas thanks to its 24 cm³ (1 HP) 2-stroke engine. Very lightweight (3.8 kg), it combines a flexible drive shaft that reduces vibration with a digital monitoring display (engine speed, usage time, maintenance alerts). Supplied with a 2-tooth blade, Autocut trimmer head and harness, it is ready to use.

• High-performance 2-stroke engine: 24 cm³ displacement delivering 1 HP to cut tall grass and brush over a 255 mm width.
• Lightweight and manoeuvrable: only 3.8 kg for extended sessions without fatigue, ideal for maintaining gardens, borders and plots far from any power outlet.
• Multifunction digital display: shows engine speed, usage time and the clock, with maintenance alerts for the filter, spark plug and gearbox.
• Working comfort: flexible drive shaft for reduced vibration, adjustable ergonomic handles and a single-strap harness that distributes the weight.
• Accessories included: 2-tooth blade and Autocut line trimmer head to alternate between grass and woody vegetation, plus a harness for immediate use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>241rr2022am</id>
      <name>RURIS RR241 BRAVO – Petrol Brush Cutter 24 cm³ 1 HP, 255 mm Cutting Width, Rigid Shaft,
        3.9 kg</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motocoase/motocoasa-ruris-241-bravo-496</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61G4VJfu2FL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81nwQf2LHaL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Brush Cutters</category>
      <price_with_vat>169.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>241rr2022am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000849</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RR241 BRAVO petrol brush cutter is designed for maintaining your garden, land or orchard. Its KHUMMA 24 cm³ (1 HP) 2-stroke engine and rigid shaft ensure optimal power transfer, even under intensive use. Lightweight (3.9 kg), it features a digital display with maintenance alerts. Supplied with a 3-tooth blade, Autocut trimmer head and a comfortable harness.

• Reliable KHUMMA-design engine: 2-stroke, 24 cm³ and 1 HP for consistent cutting of dense grass and brush over a 255 mm width.
• Rigid drive shaft: greater durability and optimal power transfer to the cutting tool, suited to intensive work and large areas.
• Smart digital display: tracks usage time and rotation speed, with maintenance alerts for the filter, spark plug and gearbox.
• Light and accessible: only 3.9 kg for prolonged use without fatigue, with a harness supplied for comfortable work on overgrown land.
• Accessories included: 3-tooth blade for woody vegetation and Autocut line trimmer head for grass, plus a harness, for immediate operation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>201RS2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 201RS – Petrol Chainsaw 1.5 HP 25.4 cc, 300 mm Guide Bar, Easy Start, Pruning</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motoferastraie-electroferastraie/motoferastrau-dac-201rs-610</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71wpndlvZ0L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71l9ybvHE+L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Chainsaws</category>
      <price_with_vat>149.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>201RS2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000931</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DAC 201RS is a lightweight 1.5 HP (25.4 cc) petrol chainsaw fitted with a 300 mm guide bar and a 3/8" 1.3 PM chain, ideal for pruning, wood carving and precision DIY work. The Easy Start system ensures quick, effortless starting, while its 2.86 kg weight guarantees excellent manoeuvrability. Fuel tank of 190 ml and oil tank of 140 ml for extended working sessions.

• TEZ 2-stroke 1.5 HP engine: 25.4 cc displacement for reliable performance on precision work, light pruning and neat finishing.
• Easy starting: the Easy Start system reduces starting effort for quick start-up, even from cold.
• 300 mm guide bar and 3/8" 1.3 PM chain: clean, stable cuts with good versatility for branches and small trunks.
• Ultra-lightweight: at just 2.86 kg, it moves easily from one position to another and limits fatigue during extended use.
• Comfortable autonomy: 190 ml fuel tank and 140 ml oil tank to keep cutting without frequent stops.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20500DAC25</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 205RS – Petrol Chainsaw 1.5 HP 25.4 cc, 200 mm Guide Bar, Easy Start, Carving</name>
      <link>https://www.amazon.es/-/en/RURIS-Thermal-Chainsaw-2-Stroke-Engine/dp/B0FS25ZHWW</link>
      <image>
        https://m.media-amazon.com/images/S/al-eu-726f4d26-7fdb/0c2fbb41-07fc-4abc-99a0-51ac359dec97.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81GuCYJyBAL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Petrol Chainsaws</category>
      <price_with_vat>169.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20500DAC25</mpn>
      <ean>5940739008562</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DAC 205RS is a compact 1.5 HP (25.4 cc) petrol chainsaw with a 200 mm guide bar and a 1/4-1.1 chain, designed for wood carving, light pruning and precision DIY work. Its Easy Start system allows effortless starting, and its low weight of 3.4 kg ensures excellent manoeuvrability. The 190 ml fuel tank and 140 ml oil tank provide good autonomy for extended sessions.

• TEZ 2-stroke 1.5 HP engine: 25.4 cc displacement for consistent performance on precision work, wood carving and delicate finishing.
• Effortless starting: the Easy Start system reduces pull resistance for quick start-up, even after a period of inactivity.
• 200 mm guide bar and 1/4-1.1 chain: clean, stable and precise cuts, ideal for detail work and small diameters.
• Light and manoeuvrable: only 3.4 kg for optimal control and prolonged, comfortable use without excessive fatigue.
• Good autonomy: 190 ml fuel tank and 140 ml oil tank to work longer without frequent stops.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>318el2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 318EL – Electric Chainsaw 1800 W, 35 cm Guide Bar, 3/8 Chain, Auto Lubrication</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motoferastraie-electroferastraie/electroferastrau-dac-318el-559</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-dac-318el-pds-40-1920-1024-0-0-559.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71T1x+y-AOL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Chainsaws</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>318el2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739000993</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DAC 318EL electric chainsaw pairs a 1800 W motor with a 35 cm guide bar to cut logs and branches quickly and cleanly. Quiet and emission-free, it suits both firewood cutting and garden pruning, with instant starting and no petrol or carburettor maintenance. Built-in chain tensioning and automatic lubrication simplify upkeep, all at a manageable weight of 4.7 kg.

• Reliable 1800 W power: high-performance electric motor driving a 35 cm guide bar for fast, clean cuts through logs and branches.
• Quiet and emission-free: instant start-up on 230 V mains power, with no petrol mix or exhaust fumes, ideal for wood-heated homes.
• 3/8 inch chain (1.3 mm): smooth, continuous cutting with reduced risk of jamming; quick chain tensioning system.
• Simplified maintenance: automatic chain lubrication and vibration limited to 5.79 m/s² for comfortable, extended work.
• Light and manoeuvrable: only 4.7 kg for easy handling when cutting firewood and pruning in the garden.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>320el2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 320EL – Electric Chainsaw 2000 W, 40 cm Bar, 3/8 Chain, Automatic Lubrication</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motoferastraie-electroferastraie/electroferastrau-dac-320el-560</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-dac-320el-pds-40-1920-1024-0-0-560.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71TPQA7KDOL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Chainsaws</category>
      <price_with_vat>69.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>320el2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001006</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DAC 320EL electric chainsaw delivers 2000 W through a 40 cm bar, making short work of logs and thicker trunks. Clean and quiet, it is ideal for firewood and regular pruning, with instant starting and no fuel or engine maintenance. The built-in chain tensioning and automatic lubrication keep upkeep to a minimum, all at a weight of 5.1 kg with accessories.

• 2000 W motor: consistent performance on all wood types, with a 40 cm bar suited to logs and thicker trunks.
• Clean and quiet: electric operation on 230 V mains power, with no petrol mix or exhaust fumes, safe to use near the house.
• 3/8-inch chain (1.3 mm): smooth, fast cutting with reduced risk of jamming thanks to the automatic tensioner.
• Minimal maintenance: built-in chain tensioning and automatic lubrication, with no carburettor or spark plug to service.
• Handy and stable: 5.1 kg with accessories for a good balance between stability and comfort during extended cutting.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>324el2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS DAC 324EL – Electric Chainsaw 2400 W, 40 cm Bar, 3/8 Chain, Automatic Lubrication</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motoferastraie-electroferastraie/electroferastrau-dac-324el-561</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-dac-324el-pds-40-1920-1024-0-0-561.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71aHfkCgXNL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Chainsaws</category>
      <price_with_vat>89.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>324el2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001013</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DAC 324EL electric chainsaw, the most powerful in the range at 2400 W, drives a 40 cm bar for clean cuts in both hardwood and softwood. Ideal for firewood and construction work, it rivals petrol models without the noise or emissions. Dampened vibrations (6.84 m/s² at the front), an easy-access tensioner and automatic lubrication ensure comfort and reduced maintenance.

• 2400 W, the most powerful in the electric range: fast, efficient cuts in hardwood or softwood with a 40 cm bar.
• Versatile: suited to bucking logs, firewood and construction work, at home or on site.
• 3/8-inch chain (1.3 mm): smooth, continuous cutting with fewer jams; easy-access tensioner.
• Enhanced comfort: dampened vibrations (6.84 m/s² at the front, 4.93 m/s² at the rear) and quiet operation for extended use.
• Instant start: 230 V mains power, with no fuel or engine maintenance; automatic chain lubrication; 5.2 kg with accessories.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>35mp2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS MP35 – 4-Stroke Petrol Water Pump for Irrigation and Water Transfer, Portable</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/motopompe-de-irigat/motopompa-ruris-mp35-546</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-mp35-water-pump-pds-42-1920-1024-0-0-546.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-mp35-water-pump-pds-42-1920-1024-0-0-546_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Petrol Water Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>121.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>35mp2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068184</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS MP35 petrol water pump handles irrigation and clean water transfer in the garden, on the farm or on site. Its 4-stroke petrol engine with manual start runs fully independently, with no need for mains electricity: ideal for watering crops, draining ponds and tanks, or pumping in remote areas. Compact and mobile at 9.1 kg, it keeps up with all your pumping needs.

• Self-contained pumping: 4-stroke petrol engine that moves large volumes of clean water without any electrical supply.
• Versatile: crop and garden irrigation, draining ponds and tanks, water transfer on the farm or on site.
• Standard fittings: suction and discharge ports in common sizes for easy connection of hoses and strainers.
• Mobile and compact: around 9.1 kg, easy to carry to the field or to remote areas, with manual recoil start.
• Designed for clean water: a reliable solution for regular agricultural watering and backup pumping, with simple maintenance.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12000EXL25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS 120EL – Electric Tiller 1200 W, 400 mm Working Width, 220 mm Depth, Electronic
        Brake</name>
      <link>
        https://www.dedeman.ro/ro/motosapa-ruris-expert-120el-model-electric-1200-w-latime-de-lucru-40-cm-roti-transport/p/7077094</link>
      <image>https://cdn.dedeman.ro/media/catalog/product/7/0/7077094.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://cdn.dedeman.ro/media/catalog/product/7/0/7077094_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Tillers</category>
      <price_with_vat>129.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12000EXL25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739064193</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 120EL electric tiller is a quiet, emission-free solution for light garden work. Its 1200 W motor loosens the soil over a 400 mm width and to a depth of 220 mm, a format ideal for small vegetable gardens, greenhouses and hard-to-reach areas. Lightweight (9.7 kg) and low in vibration, it features an electronic brake for immediate, safe stopping.

• 1200 W electric motor: all the power needed to loosen soil in gardens, greenhouses and hard-to-reach areas.
• Precise work: 400 mm working width and 220 mm depth for quickly preparing growing beds and borders.
• Enhanced safety: electronic brake that stops the tines immediately in any situation.
• Lightweight and comfortable: only 9.7 kg with low vibration, easy to use even for occasional gardeners.
• Quiet and fuel-free: mains-powered operation with no petrol or engine maintenance, ideal for residential areas.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>40440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 4044e – Cordless Tiller 2x20V Brushless, 30 cm Working Width, 6 Blades, 2x 4Ah
        Batteries Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motosapa-pe-acumulator-ruris-4044e-868</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/motosapa-pe-acumulator-ruris-4044e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-868.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>184.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>40440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033427</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 4044e is a lightweight (9.65 kg) battery-powered tiller with a 2x20V brushless motor, working the soil over a 30 cm width and to a 20 cm depth with its 6 blades. Instant starting, with no fuel or emissions: ideal for vegetable gardens, greenhouses and polytunnels. Supplied with 2 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with bidirectional USB-C charging and a USB-C cable.

• Durable brushless motor: constant power at 280 rpm with no wear parts to replace, plus a safety switch built into the handle.
• Light and agile: only 9.65 kg, 3 to 4 times lighter than a petrol tiller; instant start with no pull cord, usable in greenhouses with zero emissions.
• Efficient soil work: 30 cm width, up to 20 cm depth and 6 blades (3 left / 3 right) for quickly preparing garden and vegetable beds.
• Remarkable comfort: very low vibration (0.78 m/s²) and transport wheels adjustable across 4 positions for precise depth setting.
• 2 batteries included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah with LED display and bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank; USB-C cable supplied.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>55050rur26d</id>
      <name>RURIS 5505 – Petrol Tiller 4 HP, 4-Stroke 173 cm³ Engine, 360 mm Working Width, Compact
        27 kg</name>
      <link>https://magazinruris.ro/product/1099/motosapa-hobby-ruris-5505-4-cp.html</link>
      <image>https://magazinruris.ro/userfiles/productlargeimages/product_8677.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Tillers</category>
      <price_with_vat>265.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>55050rur26d</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020151</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 5505 petrol tiller is designed for maintaining small gardens and vegetable plots. Its General Engine 4-stroke 4 HP (173 cm³) engine with electronic ignition drives the tines through a belt transmission with an aluminium alloy housing. With a 360 mm working width, a depth of 100 to 260 mm and an average output of 400 m²/h, it is a compact machine of around 27 kg.

• Reliable engine: General Engine 4-stroke 4 HP (173 cm³) with electronic ignition and manual start, running on unleaded petrol.
• Compact format: 360 mm working width and adjustable depth from 100 to 260 mm, ideal between rows and in tight spaces.
• Protected transmission: belt drive with aluminium alloy housing and 1 forward gear, simple to use and maintain.
• Light and manoeuvrable: around 27 kg with accessories and a 0.9 L fuel tank, covering an average of 400 m² per hour.
• Ready to work: supplied with a set of tines and a user manual; 0.5 L oil sump for proper engine lubrication.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10310pis25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1031 – Adjustable Watering Gun with Connectors for Garden Hose, Adjustable Spray</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1031-796</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1031-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-796.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1031-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-796_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>12.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10310pis25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005530</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1031 adjustable watering gun attaches to your garden hose with the supplied connectors for precise, comfortable watering. Its adjustable spray switches from a concentrated jet to a fine shower as needed: delicate plants, flower beds, the vegetable garden or cleaning patios. Compact and lightweight, it offers an ergonomic grip with a flow-control trigger.

• Spray adjustable on demand: from a concentrated jet to a fine shower, so each plant gets just the right intensity.
• Versatile every day: waters lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens, and cleans patios, paths and vehicles depending on the mode chosen.
• Connectors included: fits straight onto the garden hose, with quick coupling compatible with standard watering systems.
• Compact and handy: only 0.21 kg, with an ergonomic handle and flow trigger for fatigue-free watering.
• Box contents: 1031 adjustable watering gun with quick-connect couplings.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10710pis25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1071 – Adjustable Watering Gun with Connectors, Adjustable Spray for Watering and
        Cleaning</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1071-797</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1071-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-797_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1071-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-797_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>13.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10710pis25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005547</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[With the RURIS 1071 adjustable watering gun, watering becomes precise and comfortable. Supplied with its connectors, it fits straight onto the garden hose. The spray adjusts from a fine shower to a powerful jet for watering lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens, or cleaning patios and vehicles. Its ergonomic handle with trigger lets you meter the flow effortlessly.

• Spray adjustable to the task: from a fine shower for fragile plants to a powerful jet for cleaning surfaces.
• Versatile use: ideal for watering lawns, flower beds and vegetable gardens, but also for washing patios, paths and vehicles.
• Ready to use: connectors supplied for quick coupling to the garden hose, compatible with standard watering systems.
• Ergonomic and light: comfortable handle with flow trigger, only 0.32 kg for easy, extended handling.
• Box contents: 1071 adjustable watering gun with quick-connect couplings.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10720pis25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1072 – Adjustable Watering Gun with Connectors, Multi-Mode Adjustable Spray for
        the Garden</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1072-798</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-1072-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-798.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>11.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10720pis25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005554</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1072 adjustable watering gun comes with its connectors and attaches to the garden hose in one simple move. Its adjustable spray switches from a concentrated jet to a fine shower: gentle watering of plants, flower beds and the vegetable garden, or cleaning patios and vehicles. The ergonomic handle with flow trigger ensures a comfortable, precise grip.

• Multi-mode adjustable spray: from a concentrated jet to a fine shower, matching the water's power to every garden task.
• Versatile: waters lawns, flower beds, planters and the vegetable garden, and cleans patios, paths and vehicles with the right mode.
• Connectors included: supplied with its fittings for immediate mounting on the garden hose, compatible with standard watering systems.
• Comfortable in use: ergonomic handle with flow-control trigger for precise, fatigue-free watering.
• Box contents: 1072 adjustable watering gun with quick-connect couplings.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>80000jet25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 8JET – Watering Lance with 8-Pattern Spray Head, Long Handle, for Garden Watering
        and Cleaning</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-8jet-799</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-8jet-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-799_4.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pistol-ajustabil-ruris-8jet-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-799.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>26.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>80000jet25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005561</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 8JET watering lance features a spray head with 8 selectable jet modes: rain, jet, shower, mist and more. Its long handle reaches flower beds, hanging baskets and low areas without bending down. Ideal for watering lawns, plants and planters or cleaning patios and vehicles, with an ergonomic handle and quick hose connection.

• 8 selectable spray modes: multi-pattern head (rain, jet, shower, mist and more) to suit the watering to every plant and every task.
• Versatile: waters lawns, flower beds and planters, and cleans patios, paths and vehicles with the appropriate jet.
• Practical long handle: reaches hanging baskets and low areas without bending, for comfortable watering.
• Comfortable to use: ergonomic handle with trigger and quick connection to a standard garden hose.
• Box contents: 8JET watering lance with 8-pattern spray head and long handle.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>41250rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX4125 – Cordless Angle Grinder 20V Brushless 125 mm, 2 Speeds, 4Ah Battery
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/polizor-unghiular-ruris-rmx4125-606</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx4125-angle-grinder-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-606.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71Gqg20PCCL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>95.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>41250rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034752</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX4125 cordless angle grinder cuts and grinds metal, tiles and stone thanks to its 20V brushless motor with 2 speeds (2600 and 8500 rpm) and 125 mm disc. Lightweight at 1.6 kg, it suits DIYers and tradespeople alike. Battery and charger included: an ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging and cable, plus a 125 mm disc and auxiliary handle.

• 2-speed brushless motor: 2600 rpm for sanding and finishing, 8500 rpm for cutting and roughing, with a 125 mm disc compatible with standard accessories.
• Versatile and mobile: cuts metal, tiles and stone anywhere, with no cord or socket, where a corded grinder falls short.
• Battery and charger included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C port and cable; charges from any USB-C port and doubles as a power bank for your devices.
• Safety and comfort: adjustable guard, disc-lock button for quick accessory changes, 2-position auxiliary handle and a contained weight of 1.6 kg.
• Kit contents: RMX4125 grinder, 20V 4Ah battery with LED indicator and USB-C cable, 125 mm sanding disc, auxiliary handle; the battery also powers your other RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1050ra2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RA1050 – Angle Grinder 1050 W, 125 mm Disc, 11000 rpm, Power Off, Multi-Material</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/polizor-unghiular-ruris-ra1050-621</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71URWXsCNUL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81whjjvYP2L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>49.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1050ra2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005790</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RA1050 angle grinder delivers 1050 W and 11000 rpm for cutting, grinding and polishing metal, concrete, stone and wood. Its 125 mm disc ensures fine cuts and clean finishes, while the Power Off system protects against overloads and accidental restarts. Lightweight (2.2 kg) and easy to handle, it suits everyday DIY as well as renovation work.

• 1050 W of power: effective cutting, grinding and polishing on metal, concrete, stone and wood, with a great power-to-weight ratio.
• 11000 rpm speed: fast, precise and consistent cutting, even in hard-to-reach areas.
• 125 mm disc: perfect for fine cuts, detailed adjustments and clean finishes, with excellent manoeuvrability.
• Power Off system: overload protection and a safety cut-out that prevents any accidental restart after a power interruption.
• Light and ergonomic: only 2.2 kg, with an auxiliary handle and protective guard for lasting comfort.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1100vra2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RA1100V – Angle Grinder 1000 W, 125 mm Disc, Variable Speed 3000-11000 rpm, 230 V</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/polizor-unghiular-ruris-ra1100v-622</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71gGOQ7qn8L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71v3sDuqYTL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>55.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1100vra2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005806</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RA1100V angle grinder is a versatile 1000 W power tool for cutting, grinding and polishing metal, concrete, stone and wood. Its variable speed from 3000 to 11000 rpm adapts to each material, while the switch lock reduces fatigue during extended work. Easy to handle with its 125 mm disc, it suits DIY and renovation alike, in the workshop or on site.

• 1000 W motor: constant power to cut, grind and polish metal, concrete, stone and wood efficiently.
• Variable speed 3000-11000 rpm: speed adjustable to the material being worked, for precise cuts without overheating.
• 125 mm disc: a handy format ideal for fine cuts, precise adjustments and clean finishes.
• Comfort and safety: switch lock, auxiliary handle and protective guard for controlled, less tiring work.
• Compact and light: around 2.3 kg with reduced vibration, practical for everyday DIY and renovation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1200vra2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RA1200V – Angle Grinder 1200 W, 125 mm Diamond Disc, Variable Speed, Power Off</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/polizor-unghiular-ruris-ra1200v-623</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/7148H5XYpLL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81D5L2tcVLL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1200vra2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005813</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RA1200V angle grinder pairs a 1200 W motor with a variable speed of 3000 to 11000 rpm for cutting, grinding and polishing metal, concrete, stone and wood. Supplied with a 125 mm diamond disc, it features the Power Off system against overloads and accidental restarts. A precise, safe tool for demanding renovation work, in the workshop or on site.

• 1200 W motor: a reserve of power to cut, grind and polish metal, concrete, stone and wood.
• Variable speed 3000-11000 rpm: speed matched to each material for optimal cutting without overheating.
• 125 mm diamond disc included: fine cuts, detailed adjustments and neat finishes straight out of the box.
• Power Off system: overload protection and a safety cut-out preventing any accidental restart after a power interruption.
• Ergonomic and compact: around 2.4 kg with reduced vibration, auxiliary handle and protective guard for comfortable use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2400sra2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RA2400S – Angle Grinder 2400 W, 230 mm Diamond Disc, Soft Start, 3-Position Handle</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/polizor-unghiular-ruris-ra2400s-624</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71znhqTCENL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71J+u-UneyL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>98.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2400sra2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005820</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RA2400S angle grinder is built for heavy-duty work: its 2400 W motor drives a 230 mm diamond disc to cut and grind metal, concrete and stone across large sections. The progressive Soft Start protects the motor, while the soft-grip handle adjustable across 3 positions absorbs vibration. Ideal for site work and demanding DIY.

• 2400 W of power: tackles hard materials such as metal, concrete and stone, even on large sections.
• 230 mm diamond disc included: high cutting capacity where 125 mm grinders reach their limits.
• Soft Start: smooth start-up that protects the motor from jolts and makes the tool easier to control from the moment it starts.
• 3-position adjustable soft-grip handle: absorbs vibration, reduces fatigue and ensures a firm two-handed hold.
• Enhanced safety: adjustable protective guard and ergonomic design for intensive professional use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>850ra2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RA850 – 850 W Angle Grinder, 125 mm Disc, 11000 rpm, Power Off System, Soft Grip
        Handle</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/electrice/polizor-unghiular-ruris-ra850-620</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71VL+znmd8L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71gMaptpG0L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>45.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>850ra2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739005844</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RA850 angle grinder combines an 850 W motor with a speed of 11000 rpm to cut, grind and polish metal, concrete, stone and wood. Compact and lightweight, it comes with a 125 mm diamond disc and features the Power Off system for overload protection. Its soft grip handle and adjustable guard make it a safe, comfortable tool for DIY work and small renovations.

• 850 W motor: steady power to cut, grind and polish metal, concrete, stone or wood with precision.
• 125 mm disc at 11000 rpm: ideal for fine cuts, detailed adjustments and everyday precision work.
• Power Off system: protects against overloads and prevents accidental restart after a power cut.
• Soft grip handle and reduced vibrations: comfortable hold that limits fatigue during prolonged work.
• Diamond disc included and adjustable guard: ready to use, with easy disc changes thanks to the spindle lock.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>hj-15mam</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua Pump 1100S – Self-Priming Surface Pump for Garden, Irrigation and Water
        Supply</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-de-gradina/pompa-de-grdina-874</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/garden-pump-pds-108-1920-1024-0-0-874.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>78.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>hj-15mam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068207</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua Pump 1100S self-priming surface pump supplies water to your home and garden by drawing water from a well, cistern or stream. It primes automatically, with no refilling needed at each start, and delivers a constant flow for taps, sprinklers and drip irrigation systems. Robust and easy to install, it runs on 230 V mains power.

• Self-priming: primes automatically to draw water from a well, cistern or stream, with no refilling at each start.
• Versatile use: household water supply, garden and vegetable patch irrigation, sprinklers and drip irrigation systems.
• Constant flow: designed for domestic use and regular crop watering, with reliable operation.
• Easy installation: surface pump running on 230 V mains, no immersion required, simple to connect and put into service.
• Robust and durable: reliable construction built for regular use in the garden as well as on small farms.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>jet-80bam</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua Pump 800S – 750 W Self-Priming Surface Pump, 2.9 m³/h Flow, 40 m Delivery
        Head</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-de-gradina/pompa-de-gardina-876</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pompa-de-gardina-pds-108-1920-1024-0-0-876.jpg</image>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>71.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>jet-80bam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068214</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua Pump 800S self-priming surface pump draws clean water from wells, lakes or cisterns with its 750 W single-phase 230 V motor. It delivers a flow rate of 2.9 m³/h, a delivery head of 40 m and a suction depth of 9 m. Cast iron body, bronze impeller and PPO diffuser ensure longevity. Ideal for irrigation and pressure boosting.

• 750 W motor: maximum flow of 2.9 m³/h and 40 m delivery head for water supply and irrigation.
• Suction up to 9 m: self-priming, it draws clean water from wells, lakes or cisterns without refilling at each start.
• Durable materials: cast iron body, bronze impeller and PPO diffuser for a long service life, IP44 protection.
• Versatile use: household water supply, crop irrigation and pressure boosting, up to 30 starts per hour.
• Simple installation: surface pump running on 230 V mains with a 1-inch connection, suitable for clean water up to 35 °C.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>r4skm100am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 101 – 750 W Clean Water Submersible Pump, 60 m Delivery Head, Bronze
        Impeller, Control Panel</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-101-171</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-101-pds-60-1920-1024-0-0-171.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/715NaQFnzRL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>119.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>r4skm100am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001259</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 101 submersible pump transfers clean water from drilled wells and tanks with its 750 W motor, delivering a head of 60 m and a flow rate of 2.4 m³/h. Stainless steel body, bronze impeller, oil-cooled motor and 100% copper winding guarantee a long service life. Supplied with a 15 m cable and control panel for immediate commissioning.

• Reliable performance: 750 W motor, 60 m delivery head and 2.4 m³/h flow rate to supply homes and irrigation systems.
• Versatile use: transfers clean water from drilled wells or tanks, with an immersion depth of up to 15 m.
• Premium materials: stainless steel body and bronze impeller for increased durability, even in demanding conditions.
• IP68 protection: oil-cooled motor with 100% copper winding, designed to handle up to 30 starts per hour.
• Box contents: pump, control panel and 15 m power cable for immediate installation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>qgda1.8-100-1.1am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 104 – 1100 W Borehole Submersible Pump, 100 m Delivery Head, 30 m Cable,
        Control Panel Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-104-175</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/31zJdecDXQL.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/41ygxl+i60L.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>139.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>qgda1.8-100-1.1am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001266</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 104 submersible pump supplies clean water to homes and irrigation systems from deep wells and boreholes. Its 1100 W screw-type motor delivers a head of 100 m with a flow rate of 1.8 m³/h. 4-inch stainless steel body, oil-bath motor with 100% copper winding (IP68). Supplied with control panel and 30 m power cable.

• 100 m delivery head: 1100 W screw-type motor providing a 1.8 m³/h flow rate, ideal for deep wells and boreholes.
• Domestic and agricultural use: clean water supply for homes and irrigation, compatible with a booster system.
• 4-inch stainless steel body: oil-bath-cooled motor with 100% copper winding and IP68 protection for longevity.
• Steady flow at depth: designed for clean water (particles up to 0.05 mm), immersion up to 15 m.
• Box contents: pump, control panel and long 30 m power cable for flexible installation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>4skm200am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 105 – 1500 W Borehole Submersible Pump, 140 m Delivery Head, Stainless Steel,
        30 m Cable, IP68</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-105-176</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-105-pds-60-1920-1024-0-0-176.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81t1W2J3CfL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>179.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>4skm200am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001273</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 105 submersible pump is designed for very deep wells: its 1500 W motor and 3 stages deliver an exceptional head of 140 m with a flow rate of 2.6 m³/h. 4-inch stainless steel body and oil-bath motor with 100% copper winding (IP68) for durability. Supplied with control panel and 30 m power cable.

• Exceptional 140 m delivery head: 1500 W motor and 3 pumping stages for very deep wells and high pressure.
• 2.6 m³/h flow rate: reliable clean water supply for houses, cottages and demanding irrigation systems.
• 4-inch stainless steel construction: oil-bath-cooled motor and 100% copper winding for maximum durability.
• IP68 protection: immersion up to 15 m, designed for clean water with particles up to 0.05 mm.
• Box contents: pump, control panel and 30 m power cable for installation at great depths.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>qdx1.5-25-0.55am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 11S – 550 W Clean Water Submersible Pump, 25 m Delivery Head, 3.6 m³/h Flow,
        Float Switch</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-11-166</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71qcNPbjwlL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81PHqfbxlUL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>65.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>qdx1.5-25-0.55am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001297</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 11S submersible pump supplies clean water to houses, cottages and gardens from a well, fountain or tank. Its 550 W motor delivers a head of 25 m with a flow rate of 3.6 m³/h, ideal for irrigation and drip watering. Durable aluminium body (IP68), automatic safety float switch and 15 m power cable.

• 25 m delivery head: 550 W motor delivering a 3.6 m³/h flow rate, perfect for drawing clean water from a well or tank.
• Versatile use: water supply for houses, villas and cottages, garden irrigation and drip watering systems.
• IP68 aluminium body: tough casing and impeller for durable immersion and a long, maintenance-free service life.
• Safety float switch: automatic start and stop according to the water level, with dry-running protection.
• Flexible installation: 15 m power cable to position the pump easily, even far from the socket; weight of 9 kg.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>wq1300d((f))-1am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 35 – 1300 W Dirty Water Submersible Pump with Grinder, 18 m³/h Flow, Float
        Switch, 10 m Cable</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-35-170</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71vqUCnBu4L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81cLcR72+pL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>130.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>wq1300d((f))-1am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001310</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 35 submersible pump evacuates dirty and loaded water thanks to its 1300 W motor and integrated grinder that shreds particles up to 3.5 mm. With an 18 m³/h flow rate and a 12 m delivery head, it quickly empties flooded cellars, pits, ponds and tanks. Stainless steel body, cast iron impeller, automatic safety float switch and 10 m cable.

• 1300 W of power: 18 m³/h flow rate and 12 m delivery head for fast evacuation of dirty and loaded water.
• Integrated grinder: shreds solid particles up to 3.5 mm, ideal for household wastewater, pits and flooded cellars.
• Robust construction: abrasion-resistant stainless steel body, cast iron impeller and 100% copper winding for intensive use.
• Safety float switch: automatic start and stop according to the water level, with motor protection against dry running.
• Ready to use: 10 m power cable and discharge connection compatible with standard drainage hoses.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>4qgd1.8-100-0.75am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 40 – 750 W Clean Water Borehole Submersible Pump, 100 m Delivery Head, 15 m
        Cable, Stainless Steel</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-40-169</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-40-pds-60-1920-1024-0-0-169.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/717hflFQCBL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>99.90</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>4qgd1.8-100-0.75am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001327</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 40 submersible pump extracts clean water from wells and boreholes with a delivery head of up to 100 m and a flow rate of 1.8 m³/h (1880 L/h). Its 750 W motor with 100% copper winding, oil-cooled, and stainless steel body guarantee reliability and longevity. Ideal for supplying homes and irrigation; supplied with a 15 m cable and 1-inch connection.

• Delivery head up to 100 m: 750 W motor with 100% copper winding to pump clean water from deep wells and boreholes.
• Versatile use: water supply for houses, villas and cottages, irrigation of small crops and drip watering systems.
• 1.8 m³/h flow rate: reliable water extraction from wells, tanks or ponds, with an immersion depth of up to 15 m.
• Durable construction: corrosion-resistant stainless steel body and oil-cooled motor for a long, maintenance-free service life.
• Simple installation: 15 m power cable supplied, 4-inch diameter and 1-inch discharge connection for any domestic system.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>3stm3-14am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 690 – 370 W Borehole Submersible Pump, 14 Stages, 60 m Delivery Head, 25 m
        Cable</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-690-174</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61GXwyUCSCL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71gQIzTY7jL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>148.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>3stm3-14am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001334</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 690 submersible pump is a 14-stage multistage borehole pump, ideal for narrow 3-inch wells. Its 370 W motor delivers a head of 60 m with a flow rate of 3 m³/h to supply clean water to homes and pressurised irrigation systems. Stainless steel body, PPO impeller, oil-bath motor (IP68). Supplied with control panel and 25 m cable.

• 14 pumping stages: 370 W motor delivering a 60 m head and a 3 m³/h flow rate at constant pressure.
• Designed for narrow wells: 3-inch diameter, perfect for small-diameter boreholes, with immersion up to 15 m.
• Durable construction: stainless steel body, PPO technopolymer impeller and oil-bath-cooled motor for maintenance-free use.
• IP68 protection: 100% copper winding and full watertightness for reliable operation during prolonged immersion.
• Box contents: pump, control panel and 25 m power cable for quick commissioning.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>4stm2-8am</id>
      <name>RURIS Aqua 790 – 550 W Borehole Submersible Pump, 8 Stages, 60 m Delivery Head, 25 m
        Cable</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pompe-submersibile/pompa-submersibila-ruris-aqua-790-178</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61xnZ3CL0sL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71JXtXtZd2L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Pumps &gt; Submersible Pumps</category>
      <price_with_vat>145.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>4stm2-8am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001341</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Aqua 790 submersible pump draws clean water from deep wells and boreholes with its 550 W motor and 8 pumping stages, delivering a 60 m head and a constant flow of 3 m³/h. 4-inch stainless steel body, PPO impeller and oil-bath motor (IP68, 100% copper winding). Supplied with control panel and 25 m power cable.

• 8 pumping stages: 550 W motor delivering a 60 m head and a 3 m³/h flow rate at constant pressure.
• Versatile use: clean water supply for homes, cottages and irrigation systems from 4-inch wells and boreholes.
• Durable construction: stainless steel body, PPO technopolymer impeller and oil-bath-cooled motor, all corrosion resistant.
• Suited to clean water: particles up to 0.05 mm and sand tolerance of 150 g/m³, IP68 protection, immersion up to 15 m.
• Box contents: pump, control panel and 25 m power cable for a ready-to-use installation.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>61200pid25a</id>
      <name>RURIS DIG612 – Digital LCD Watering Timer, 1-360 min Timer, G3/4 and G1 Adapters</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/programator-digital-irigare-ruris-dig612-800</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/programator-digital-irigare-ruris-dig612-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-800.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71E36CwED+L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>32.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>61200pid25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006001</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS DIG612 digital watering timer automates garden irrigation: watering duration adjustable from 1 to 360 minutes and frequency from every 6 or 12 hours up to every 1 to 7 days. Its large LCD screen and big buttons make setup easy, with manual control and a start-delay function. Made of ABS and TPR, it operates at 4 to 6 bar with 2 AA batteries (not included). Supplied with a G3/4 reducer and a G1 tap adapter.

• Flexible programming: watering duration from 1 to 360 minutes and frequency adjustable to every 6 h, 12 h or 1 to 7 days, suited to every crop and season.
• Simple to use: large LCD screen readable in all conditions and big buttons that are easy to operate, even with wet hands.
• Full control: manually trigger a one-off watering without changing the current programme, plus a delay function to choose the start time.
• Built for outdoor use: tough ABS and TPR housing, working pressure of 4 to 6 bar, temperature range of 5 to 35 °C; runs on 2 AA batteries (not included).
• Box contents: timer, G3/4 reducer (26.4 mm) and G1 tap adapter (33.2 mm) for universal tool-free mounting.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20000pim25a</id>
      <name>RURIS M2 – Manual Watering Timer for Garden Taps, Battery-Free, Automatic Shut-Off</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/programator-irigare-manual-ruris-m2-801</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/programator-irigare-manual-ruris-m2-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-801.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/programator-irigare-manual-ruris-m2-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-801.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>11.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20000pim25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006018</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS M2 manual watering timer connects directly to the garden tap and automatically shuts off the water after the set time. Fully mechanical, it works without batteries and manages the supply to sprinklers and drip irrigation systems without constant supervision. A simple solution to save water and organise the watering of your vegetable patch and lawn alike.

• Controlled watering: set the desired watering time and the water shuts off automatically at the end, no supervision needed.
• Compatible: manages the supply to sprinklers, soaker hoses and drip irrigation systems connected to the garden tap.
• Mechanical operation: manual timer with no batteries or electronics, simple and reliable season after season.
• Water savings: prevents waste and forgotten taps by stopping the watering exactly at the set time.
• Immediate installation: screws onto the garden tap without tools, very lightweight (0.21 kg) and easy to use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>18000RSE25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RSE 1800PRO – 18 L Electric Backpack Sprayer, 6 bar, Telescopic Lance, Battery Not
        Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse1800pro-654</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse1800pro-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-654.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71cWQ1nogjL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>69.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>18000RSE25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739063301</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RSE 1800PRO electric backpack sprayer delivers constant spraying at 6 bar with a flow rate of 4.5 L/min, ideal for gardens, orchards and vegetable crops. Its 18 L tank and metal telescopic lance with 4 interchangeable nozzles cover every type of treatment. Runs on a 20V 4Ah Li-Ion battery providing 2.5 h of runtime — battery and charger sold separately.

• Constant, effective pressure: 6 bar electric motor with a robust diaphragm pump and 4.5 L/min flow rate for uniform spraying, even on dense foliage.
• Long working autonomy: 18 L tank and up to 2.5 h of operation per charge, to treat gardens, orchards and medium-sized farms without interruption.
• Telescopic lance and 4 nozzles: length-adjustable metal lance and interchangeable nozzles (1, 2, 4 and 5 outlets) to adapt the spray to each crop and height.
• Comfort and control: LED battery level display, automatic solution mixing and ergonomic straps distributing the weight (3.8 kg net).
• No battery or charger included: runs on the RURIS 20V 4Ah Li-Ion battery, sold separately. Contents: sprayer, telescopic lance, 4 nozzles, high-pressure hose.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>19000RSE25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RSE 1900S – 18 L Electric Backpack Sprayer, 12V 8Ah Battery, 6 bar, Telescopic
        Lance</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse1900s-666</link>
      <image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71N-vM7huXL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/7160JwzfOZL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>58.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>19000RSE25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006148</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RSE 1900S electric backpack sprayer is designed for applying plant protection treatments and liquid fertilisers in the garden, orchard and vegetable patch. Its pump delivers a constant pressure of 6 bar with a flow rate of 2.9 L/min, and its built-in 12V 8Ah battery provides up to 4 hours of runtime. An 18 L tank, metal telescopic lance, LED display, automatic mixing and 5 interchangeable nozzles complete the equipment.

• Constant performance: 6 bar (87 PSI) pressure and 2.9 L/min flow rate for even, deep coverage of your crops.
• Long runtime: built-in 12V 8Ah battery providing up to 4 hours of continuous use, with no manual pumping effort.
• Large 18 L tank: reduces refill stops and lets you treat gardens, orchards and vegetable patches in extended sessions.
• Practical technology: LED battery monitoring display, leak-proof copper connector, high-pressure hose and automatic solution mixing.
• Box contents: 18 L sprayer with built-in battery and charger, metal telescopic lance and 5 nozzles (standard, 2-outlet, 3-outlet metal, 4-zone, 8-zone).]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>200000RSE25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RSE 200 – Electric Sprayer 2 L, 2 Bar, Built-In 3.7V 2Ah Battery, USB-C, LED
        Display</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse200-676</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse200-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-676.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-electric-ruris-rse200-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-676_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>26.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>200000RSE25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739066357</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RSE 200 electric sprayer eliminates manual pumping: its motor, powered by a built-in 3.7V 2Ah battery, delivers a constant pressure of 2 bar. The LED display shows the charge level in real time, and recharging is done via the included USB-C cable. With its 2 L tank and nozzle adjustable from a concentrated jet to a fine mist, it is ideal for regular treatments in the garden, greenhouse or indoors.

• Effortless electric spraying: the motor maintains a constant pressure of 2 bar with no manual pumping, for even application of treatments and disinfectants.
• Built-in 3.7V 2Ah battery with USB-C charging: USB-C cable included for easy recharging from any USB port, with no need for mains power while you work.
• LED charge indicator display: the battery level is shown in real time so you can plan your sessions and avoid unexpected interruptions.
• Adjustable nozzle and On/Off button: from a concentrated jet to fine spraying, with instant start and stop without holding a trigger.
• Compact and lightweight: 2 L tank, 0.45 kg empty and 2.45 kg full, ideal for plants, the greenhouse and tight spaces.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2000rs19am</id>
      <name>RURIS RS 2000 – Electric and Manual Sprayer 20 L, 12V 8Ah Battery and Charger Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-electric-manual-367</link>
      <image>
        https://m.media-amazon.com/images/S/al-eu-726f4d26-7fdb/65fa0497-6f06-4fb1-b37f-16e911367d22.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71Y2g3MCRCL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>54.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2000rs19am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006223</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RS 2000 backpack sprayer combines electric and manual operation to adapt to every work session. Its 12V 8Ah battery, supplied with its charger, provides up to 4 hours of runtime, with a flow rate of 3.1 L/min at 5.5 bar (80 PSI) for uniform application of fertilisers and treatments. A transparent 20 L tank and a telescopic metal lance complete this versatile piece of equipment for gardeners and professionals.

• Dual electric and manual operation: maximum flexibility for long sessions as well as quick, one-off jobs in the garden.
• Battery and charger included: 12V 8Ah battery providing up to 4 hours of continuous use, with no pumping effort while you work.
• Uniform application: flow rate of 3.1 L/min at 5.5 bar (80 PSI) for even distribution of liquid fertilisers and plant-protection solutions.
• Transparent 20 L tank: visual check of the solution level and safe refilling for treating large areas.
• Telescopic metal lance: sturdy and length-adjustable for precise spraying at different heights.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>10000RSS25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RS 100 – Manual Sprayer 1 L, 2 Bar Pressure, Adjustable Copper Nozzle, Stainless
        Steel Rod</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs100-650</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs100-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-650.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs100-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-650_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>6.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>10000RSS25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739066333</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RS 100 1 L manual sprayer delivers a fine, uniform spray at 2 bar, ideal for precisely treating plants, seedlings and small areas in the garden, in the greenhouse or indoors. Its adjustable copper nozzle switches from a concentrated jet to a fine mist, and the locking handle keeps the flow constant without fatigue. Stainless steel rod resistant to corrosion; only 0.32 kg empty.

• Precise spraying at 2 bar: steady working pressure for applying plant-protection products, liquid fertilisers or disinfectants evenly, without wasting solution.
• Adjustable copper nozzle: switch from a concentrated jet to fine spraying to suit the type of plant and the surface being treated.
• Locking handle: the trigger lock keeps the flow constant without continuous hand pressure, for repeated treatments without fatigue.
• Stainless steel rod: resistant to corrosion from common plant-protection solutions, for durability superior to plastic rods.
• Compact and easy to handle: 1 L tank and a weight of 0.32 kg empty, perfect for the garden, the greenhouse and tight spaces; works without electricity or batteries.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>11000RS026A</id>
      <name>RURIS RS 1000S – Manual Backpack Sprayer 10 L, 2-3 Bar, Metal Lance, Safety Valve</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs1000s-854</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs1000s-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-854.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs1000s-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-854_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>17.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>11000RS026A</mpn>
      <ean>5940739021639</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RS 1000S manual backpack sprayer combines a 10 L tank with a built-in pump delivering 2 to 3 bar (0.2-0.3 MPa) to treat the garden, vegetable patch and orchard without electricity or batteries. Its automatic safety valve protects against overpressure, and the funnel-shaped filling opening prevents spills. Ultra-light when empty (1.4 kg), it is carried comfortably thanks to its reinforced straps.

• 10 L tank: capacity suited to treating large areas in the garden, vegetable patch or orchard without frequent refills.
• Controlled 2-3 bar pressure with safety valve: uniform application of plant-protection products and fertilisers, with automatic protection against overpressure.
• Durable metal lance: resistant to wear and chemicals, for precise, even spraying over time.
• Carrying comfort: only 1.4 kg empty, reinforced straps distributing the weight of the full tank (11.4 kg) and an ergonomic handle.
• Easy filling and total independence: large funnel-shaped opening for pouring without spills; works without electricity or batteries, always ready to use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1600rs2018am</id>
      <name>RURIS RS 1600 – Manual Backpack Sprayer 16 L, Transparent Tank, Telescopic Metal Lance</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs1600-244</link>
      <image>
        https://m.media-amazon.com/images/S/al-eu-726f4d26-7fdb/654f9377-a9fd-4616-9bfb-e6835f4f5add.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71CSEB-iHuL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>33.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1600rs2018am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006261</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RS 1600 manual backpack sprayer lets you apply liquid fertilisers and plant-protection solutions in the garden, vegetable patch, orchard or greenhouse. Its transparent 16 L tank shows the remaining solution level, and its telescopic metal lance ensures precise, targeted spraying. Lightweight (3.8 kg), it is carried comfortably thanks to heavy-duty straps and withstands corrosive products with minimal maintenance.

• Even spraying: the manual pressure system delivers liquid fertilisers and plant-protection treatments evenly over plants and crops.
• Versatile: suitable for the garden, vegetable patch, orchard, greenhouse and for disinfection or pest-control operations in outdoor spaces.
• Transparent 16 L tank: easy check of the remaining solution level and long working autonomy with fewer refills.
• Carrying comfort: heavy-duty back straps and an ergonomic handle for extended sessions without fatigue, with a contained weight of 3.8 kg.
• Durable and easy to maintain: sturdy materials resistant to corrosive substances and a telescopic metal lance adjustable in length.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>80000RS025Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RS 800S – Manual Backpack Sprayer 8 L, 2-3 Bar Pressure, Metal Lance, Garden and
        Vegetable Patch</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs800s-678</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs800s-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-678.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pulverizator-manual-ruris-rs800s-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-678_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>15.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>80000RS025Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739064209</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RS 800S manual backpack sprayer is a lightweight, practical tool for applying plant-protection products and liquid fertilisers to small and medium areas, in the garden, vegetable patch or greenhouse. Its 8 L tank and working pressure of 2 to 3 bar (0.2-0.3 MPa) ensure even distribution, while the metal lance and heavy-duty straps guarantee durability and carrying comfort.

• 8 L tank: ideal capacity for regular treatments in the garden, vegetable patch or greenhouse, without overly frequent refills.
• 2-3 bar working pressure: the manual pump ensures efficient, even distribution of plant-protection products and liquid fertilisers.
• Durable metal lance: resistant to wear and chemicals, for precise spraying throughout the appliance's lifetime.
• Comfortable carrying: heavy-duty straps and an ergonomic design for wearing the sprayer on your back during long work sessions.
• Total independence: 100% manual operation, without electricity or batteries, always ready to use for caring for plants and crops.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20000lzn25a</id>
      <name>RURIS LuxuryZn – 2-Way Metal Connector for Garden Tap, Adjustable Flow on Each Outlet</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/racord-luxury-zn-793</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/racord-luxury-zn-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-793.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://www.ruris.ro/racord-luxury-zn-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-793_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>17.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20000lzn25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006292</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS LuxuryZn 2-way metal connector screws onto the garden tap to feed two hoses or watering accessories simultaneously. Each outlet has an independent adjustment dial to open, close or regulate the flow. Its sturdy metal construction and reinforced sealing make it reliable equipment for intensive use in the garden.

• Two outlets from a single tap: feeds two hoses simultaneously, or one hose and a drip system, to manage two watering zones.
• Independent adjustable flow: each outlet has its own dial to open, close or regulate the water separately as needed.
• Metal construction: durable metal body for intensive, long-lasting use, far sturdier than plastic connectors.
• Watertight and reliable: standard garden-tap thread and reinforced leak-free sealing; tool-free installation.
• Box contents: LuxuryZn 2-way metal connector to screw onto the tap.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>18080rxe26a</id>
      <name>RURIS RXE 1808E – Electric Scarifier and Aerator 1800 W, 38 cm Working Width, 45 L Bag,
        2 Rollers</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/scarificator-gazon-electric-885</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/scarificator-gazon-electric-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-885.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/scarificator-gazon-electric-pds-57-1920-1024-0-0-885_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Electric Lawn Mowers</category>
      <price_with_vat>119.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>18080rxe26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020212</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RXE 1808E electric lawn scarifier revives your lawn with its two functions: scarifying with a 16-blade roller and aerating with a 24-spring roller, easily interchangeable. Its 1800 W motor works across a 38 cm width, with 5 adjustable heights from -12 to +6 mm. The 45 L collection bag gathers moss and thatch for a healthy, dense lawn.

• 1800 W motor: enough power to scarify and aerate residential lawns effectively, with instant mains start-up.
• 2-in-1 dual function: 16-blade roller for scarifying and removing thatch, 24-spring roller for aerating the soil, interchangeable without complicated tools.
• 38 cm working width: covers medium-sized areas quickly to regenerate the entire lawn in just a few passes.
• 5 adjustable working heights: from -12 to +6 mm to match the depth to the type of lawn and soil condition, from light combing to deep dethatching.
• 45 L collection bag: large capacity for gathering moss and debris without frequent interruptions, leaving the lawn clean after each pass.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12000set25a</id>
      <name>RURIS Set 12 – Connector Kit for 1/2" Garden Hose, Quick-Fit Couplings, Tool-Free
        Assembly</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/set-conectori-furtun-ruris-12-792</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/set-conectori-furtun-ruris-12-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-792.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>8.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12000set25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006384</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Set 12 brings together the connectors needed to fit out a 1/2 inch garden hose: quick-fit couplings for connecting hose, spray gun and tap in seconds. The click-on connections ensure reinforced, leak-free sealing and fully tool-free assembly. The complete solution for setting up or extending the garden watering system.

• Complete 1/2 inch kit: all the couplings needed to connect hose, spray gun and tap and set up garden watering.
• Tool-free assembly: click-on connections for one-step fitting and removal that anyone can manage.
• Reinforced sealing: couplings designed for reliable, leak-free connections, compatible with standard watering systems.
• Practical and expandable: ideal for installing a first watering system or replacing worn couplings on existing equipment.
• Box contents: 1/2 inch connector set (quick-fit couplings for hose, spray gun and tap).]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>33000RSW25Aam</id>
      <name>RURIS RSE 33 Easy Way – Portable Electric Sprayer, Li-Ion Battery, 3 m Hose, USB-C</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/aparate-de-stropit-pulverizatoare/sistem-de-pulverizare-electric-ruris-rse33-easyway-656</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/sistem-de-pulverizare-electric-ruris-rse33-easyway-pds-64-1920-1024-0-0-656.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71GOZYVpNTL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Sprayers</category>
      <price_with_vat>29.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>33000RSW25Aam</mpn>
      <ean>5940739061789</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RSE 33 Easy Way is a portable electric spraying system that draws the solution directly from a container or a water source through its suction filter. Its built-in 2600 mAh Li-Ion battery, rechargeable via USB-C, powers constant, effortless spraying. Adjustable nozzle from a concentrated jet to a fine mist, metal lance, 3 m hose and an LED display with battery indicator: lightweight, it is ideal for garden treatments.

• Effortless spraying: electric motor powered by a built-in 2600 mAh Li-Ion battery, with quick and convenient recharging via the USB Type C port.
• Adjustable nozzle: switches easily from a concentrated jet to a fine mist to treat plants, vegetable patches, hedges and other garden areas with precision.
• Freedom of movement: rigid metal lance and 3 m flexible hose for working at a distance from the container without frequent repositioning.
• Versatile use: the suction filter allows the liquid to be pumped from a container or directly from a natural source.
• Simple and lightweight: LED display with battery level indicator, one-touch On/Off control and a weight of just 576 g for easy home use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1100qr21am</id>
      <name>RURIS CleanPowerJet 1100 – High-Pressure Washer 1400 W, 110 Bar, 390 L/h, Accessories
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/spalatoare-cu-presiune/spalator-ruris-cleanpowerjet-1100-423</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-cleanpowerjet-1100-pressure-washer-pds-75-1920-1024-0-0-423.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Pressure Washers</category>
      <price_with_vat>79.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1100qr21am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068245</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS CleanPowerJet 1100 high-pressure washer is the ideal compact model for everyday cleaning jobs in the garden and around the house. Its 1400 W motor delivers up to 110 bar with a flow rate of 390 l/h for cleaning paving, patios, tools and vehicles. The lance set and foam function adapt to every surface. Supplied with spray gun, lances, spray nozzle and hose.

• Compact and efficient: 1400 W motor delivering a maximum pressure of 110 bar and a flow rate of 390 l/h for daily cleaning.
• Versatile: ideal for cleaning paving, patios, garden furniture, bikes, tools and cars around the house.
• Adaptable jet: interchangeable lances and foam function to adjust the jet power to the type of surface and dirt.
• Built to last: quick-fit connector with integrated filter protecting the pump and 360° hose rotation preventing premature wear.
• Box contents: washer, spray gun, lances, spray nozzle and high-pressure hose; 230 V power supply, lightweight and easy to store.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1300qr21am</id>
      <name>RURIS CleanPowerJet 1300 – High-Pressure Washer 1600 W, 130 Bar, 7 L/min, 6 m Hose</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/spalatoare-cu-presiune/spalator-ruris-cleanpowerjet-1300-424</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-cleanpowerjet-1300-pressure-washer-pds-75-1920-1024-0-0-424.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Pressure Washers</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1300qr21am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068252</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS CleanPowerJet 1300 high-pressure washer effortlessly cleans yards, paving, garden furniture and vehicles. Its 1600 W motor delivers up to 130 bar and a flow rate of 7 l/min, with no technical knowledge required. The adjustable lance and active foam adapt to every kind of dirt, while the quick-fit connector with filter protects the pump. Supplied with spray gun, lances, spray nozzle and a 6 m hose. Weight: 6 kg.

• Powerful cleaning: 1600 W motor developing 130 bar and a flow rate of 7 l/min to remove dirt from paving, yards, facades and vehicles.
• Easy to use: quick connection to the water supply and immediate handling, even without technical experience.
• Adaptable jet: adjustable lance and active foam function to tailor the cleaning to the type of surface and dirt.
• Durable: 360° hose rotation in the gun preventing kinks and wear; quick-fit connector with integrated filter protecting the pump.
• Box contents: washer, spray gun, lances, spray nozzle and 6 m hose; 5 m power cable; 6 kg, compact and easy to store.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1500qr21am</id>
      <name>RURIS CleanPowerJet 1500 – High-Pressure Washer 2000 W, 160 Bar, 7.5 L/min, Turbo Jet
        Lance</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/spalatoare-cu-presiune/spalator-ruris-cleanpowerjet-1500-425</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/spalator-ruris-cleanpowerjet-1500-pds-75-1920-1024-0-0-425.jpg</image>
      <category>Tools &gt; Pressure Washers</category>
      <price_with_vat>149.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1500qr21am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068269</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS CleanPowerJet 1500 high-pressure washer tackles stubborn dirt on paving, facades, patios and vehicles. Its 2000 W motor develops up to 160 bar (110 bar nominal) with a flow rate of 7.5 l/min. The adjustable lance, rotating Turbo Jet lance and active foam tank adapt to every surface. Wheel-mounted, supplied with spray gun, angled-nozzle extension, spray nozzle, brush and a 6 m hose.

• High performance: 2000 W motor delivering up to 160 bar (110 bar nominal) and 7.5 l/min to dislodge the most stubborn dirt.
• Versatile: effectively cleans grimy paving, facades, patios, garden furniture and cars where entry-level models fail.
• Rotating Turbo Jet lance: maximum coverage for heavily soiled surfaces, with an integrated active foam tank for car washing.
• Practical and durable: moves on wheels, 360° hose rotation in the gun and a quick-fit connector with filter protecting the pump.
• Box contents: washer, spray gun, angled-nozzle extension, Turbo Jet lance, spray nozzle, brush and 6 m hose; 5 m cable; 8.6 kg.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12240rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 1224e – Cordless Leaf Blower 20V, 40 m/s, 570 m³/h, 2.75 kg, Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/suflanta-ruris-1224e-568</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/suflanta-ruris-1224e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-568.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>70.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12240rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034721</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1224e is a compact, ultra-light (2.75 kg) 20V cordless leaf blower with an air speed of 40 m/s and an air flow of 570 m³/h. It moves dead leaves, grass clippings and small debris on paths, patios and lawns, with no cable or fuel. Supplied with an ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with bidirectional USB-C charging and a USB-C cable.

• Efficient cleaning: air speed of 40 m/s and air flow of 570 m³/h to move leaves, grass clippings and small debris on paths, patios and lawns.
• Ideal for small spaces: perfect for balconies, patios and small gardens, with quick cleaning without excessive noise or the constraints of a cable or fuel.
• Very lightweight: only 2.75 kg for frequent use without fatigue, with instant start at the press of a button.
• Battery included with USB-C charging: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery rechargeable from any USB-C port without a mains charger; also works as a power bank for your devices.
• Box contents: 1224e blower with tube fitted, ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah battery with 3-level LED display, USB-C cable.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12640rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS VoltX 1264e – 60V Brushless Blower, 1200 m³/h, 72 m/s, Turbo, Battery and Charger
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/suflanta-ruris-voltx-1264e-862</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/suflanta-ruris-voltx-1264e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-862.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>249.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12640rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033496</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS VoltX 1264e is a 60V cordless blower with a brushless motor (25,000 rpm) delivering 1200 m³/h and 72 m/s: it moves wet leaves and heavy debris across large yards, driveways and car parks. 3 speeds, a Turbo function and a variable-speed trigger for precise control. Supplied with an ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah battery and charger included.

• 60V power: brushless motor at 25,000 rpm delivering an air flow of 1200 m³/h and 72 m/s, capable of moving wet leaves, light gravel and heavy debris.
• Precise control: 3 speeds plus a Turbo function and a variable-speed trigger, from cleaning delicate surfaces to quickly covering large areas.
• Ideal for large areas: designed for yards, driveways and car parks of 200 to 1000 m², without the fuel constraints of a petrol blower.
• Comfortable to use: Soft Grip handle, vibrations limited to 2.15 m/s² and a contained weight of 4.5 kg for extended sessions.
• Battery and charger included: RURIS ALFA UP 6400e 60V 4Ah Li-Ion battery (240 Wh) with digital display, compatible with all tools in the VoltX range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12440rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 1244e – 3-in-1 Cordless Blower Vacuum Shredder 2x20V, 80 m/s, 45 L Bag, 2
        Batteries Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/suflanta-ruris-1224e-568</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/suflantaaspirator-pe-acumulator-ruris-1244e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-866.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>137.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12440rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739033472</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1244e is a 3-in-1 cordless blower, vacuum and shredder with a 2x20V brushless motor (160 Wh): it blows at 80 m/s (650 m³/h), vacuums leaves and shreds them at a 12:1 ratio into its 45 L bag. Lightweight (3.5 kg) with a shoulder strap and adjustable handle, it is ideal for medium-sized gardens. Comes with 2 ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries with USB-C charging.

• 3 functions in 1: blow, vacuum and shred leaves with a single tool thanks to the 2x20V brushless motor running at 17,000 rpm (80 m/s, 650 m³/h).
• 12:1 shredding: greatly reduces the volume of garden waste collected in the 45 L bag, meaning fewer trips to the composter.
• Controlled airflow: 4 speeds plus a Turbo function to match the power to paths, lawns and patios, especially during autumn clean-up.
• Light and comfortable: 3.5 kg with accessories, shoulder strap and adjustable secondary handle for extended use without fatigue.
• 2 batteries included: ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah with 21700 cells and bidirectional USB-C charging, also usable as a power bank; USB-C cable supplied.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>600rtx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RTX 600 – Petrol Cut-Off Saw 58 cc 3.3 HP, 300 mm Disc, 100 mm Cutting Depth</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/masini-de-taiat-beton-si-asfalt/taietor-beton-ruris-rtx600-547</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/taietor-beton-ruris-rtx600-pds-84-1920-1024-0-0-547_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/taietor-beton-ruris-rtx600-pds-84-1920-1024-0-0-547_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Construction &gt; Construction Machinery</category>
      <price_with_vat>547.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>600rtx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068276</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RTX 600 petrol cut-off saw cuts concrete, asphalt, stone and metal right on the job site, with no cable or power supply needed. Its 58 cc 2-stroke engine (3.3 HP, up to 8500 rpm) drives a 300 mm disc at 4800 rpm, delivering a cutting depth of 100 mm. Lightweight (10.1 kg) and easy to handle, it runs on a petrol-oil mix (25 ml/L) with a 750 ml fuel tank.

• Powerful cutting: 58 cc, 3.3 HP 2-stroke engine driving the 300 mm disc at 4800 rpm, with a cutting depth of up to 100 mm.
• Versatile: cuts concrete, asphalt, stone, slabs, kerbs, pavers, pipes and metal profiles on construction sites and roadworks.
• Fully autonomous: petrol operation with no cable, engine speed up to 8500 rpm, 750 ml tank for the fuel mix (25 ml of oil per litre of petrol).
• Light and manoeuvrable: only 10.1 kg for longer working sessions and access to hard-to-reach areas; manual start.
• Built for the job site: compact disc cutter for construction, renovation and road work, for professionals and homeowners alike.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>12150tmb25a</id>
      <name>RURIS 1215 PP – Hose Reel with 15 m 1/2" Garden Hose, Wall-Mountable, Nozzle and
        Connectors Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/conectica-gradina/tambur-cu-furtun-ruris-1215pp-794</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/tambur-cu-furtun-ruris-1215pp-pds-98-1920-1024-0-0-794_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81cpgqS4sqL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Watering Accessories</category>
      <price_with_vat>29.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>12150tmb25a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739006490</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 1215 PP hose reel comes with an integrated 15-metre 1/2 inch garden hose, for a tidy garden and watering straight out of the box. Made of polypropylene, ABS and PVC, it withstands outdoor conditions and operates at 4 to 6 bar. Compact (30 x 26 x 27.5 cm) and lightweight, it can be placed freely or fixed to the wall with the 4 screws included. Watering nozzle, 1/2 inch connector and STOP connector supplied.

• Ready to water: hose reel supplied with an integrated 15 m, 1/2 inch (13 mm) hose, ready to use straight out of the box.
• Tidy storage: the hose winds up neatly after every use — no more knots or hoses lying around the garden.
• Durable construction: weather-resistant polypropylene, ABS and PVC; working pressure of 4 to 6 bar, temperature range 5 to 35 °C.
• Compact and wall-mountable: dimensions 30 x 26 x 27.5 cm at 2.86 kg, with 4 wall-mounting screws included for a stable installation.
• Box contents: reel with 15 m hose, 1/2 inch connector, 1/2 inch STOP connector, watering nozzle and 4 wall-mounting screws.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>150st2023am</id>
      <name>RURIS Expert 150 – Electric Garden Shredder 2600 W, 45 mm Branches, 45 L Collection Box,
        2 Wheels</name>
      <link>
        https://www.dedeman.ro/ro/tocator-crengi-si-resturi-vegetale-ruris-expert-150-electric-recipient-colector-45-l/p/7073227</link>
      <image>https://cdn.dedeman.ro/media/catalog/product/7/0/7073227.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://cdn.dedeman.ro/media/catalog/product/7/0/7073227_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Garden Shredders</category>
      <price_with_vat>159.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>150st2023am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739066364</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS Expert 150 electric garden shredder chops branches, twigs and leaves up to 45 mm in diameter with its 2600 W motor (230 V mains) running at 4500 rpm. Its integrated 45 L collection box reduces how often you need to empty it, and its two sturdy wheels make it easy to move around the garden. Lightweight (12.1 kg), it produces chips ready to use as mulch or compost.

• 2600 W and 4500 rpm: 230 V mains-powered electric motor that continuously shreds branches, leaves and green waste without losing speed.
• Branches up to 45 mm: suited to pruning waste from fruit trees, hedges and ornamental shrubs in gardens with regular output.
• 45 L collection box: catches the chips directly beneath the machine and reduces the number of emptying stops while you work.
• Easy to move: two sturdy wheels and a contained weight of 12.1 kg let you move the shredder without carrying it, even on unpaved ground.
• Usable chips: the shredded material can be used as mulch to suppress weeds and retain moisture, or added to compost.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>100s2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS ST100S – Electric Garden Shredder 2400 W, 40 mm Branches, 50 L Bag, 4500 rpm</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/tocatoare-de-crengi/tocator-de-crengi-ruris-st100s-421</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/tocator-de-crengi-ruris-st100s-pds-74-1920-1024-0-0-421.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71TAojw+3KL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Garden Shredders</category>
      <price_with_vat>137.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>100s2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001617</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ST100S electric garden shredder turns branches and green waste into chips you can reuse as mulch or compost. Its 2400 W motor running at 4500 rpm shreds branches up to 40 mm in diameter, ideal for maintaining medium-sized gardens. Compact and quiet, it comes with a 50 L collection bag and moves easily thanks to its metal chassis on two wheels.

• Optimal power: 2400 W electric motor with a rotation speed of 4500 rpm for high shredding performance.
• Cutting capacity: shreds branches and garden waste up to 40 mm in diameter, perfect for pruning hedges, shrubs and fruit trees.
• Built-in protection: overload protection system that safeguards the motor and extends the machine's service life.
• Clean work: 50 L collection bag to gather the chips, ready to reuse directly as mulch or in compost.
• Easy transport: stable metal chassis and two sturdy wheels to move the shredder effortlessly around the whole garden.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>200s2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS ST200S – Electric Garden Shredder 2800 W, 45 mm Branches, 60 L Locking Collection
        Box</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/tocatoare-de-crengi/tocator-de-crengi-ruris-st200s-422</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/tocator-de-crengi-ruris-st200s-pds-74-1920-1024-0-0-422.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71oQw2w+GsL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Garden Shredders</category>
      <price_with_vat>235.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>200s2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001624</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS ST200S electric garden shredder efficiently reduces pruning waste thanks to its 2800 W motor and durable blades, capable of shredding branches up to 45 mm in diameter. Its 60 L collection box with a secure locking system only allows operation when the box is closed. Quiet and suitable for residential areas, it moves easily on its two wheels and stable chassis.

• High shredding power: robust 2800 W motor and durable blades to easily shred branches up to 45 mm in diameter.
• Enhanced safety: the shredder only runs when the 60 L collection box is properly closed and locked.
• Comfortable to use: quiet operation, suitable for residential areas without disturbing the neighbours.
• Motor protection: built-in overload protection system that preserves the machine's performance over the long term.
• Optimal mobility: two solid wheels and a stable frame to move the shredder easily around the garden.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>40012016am</id>
      <name>RURIS TE400 – Electric Grass Trimmer 400 W, 200 mm Cutting Width, Telescopic Shaft,
        Lightweight 1.2 kg</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/trimmer-electric-ruris-te400-154</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/trimmer-electric-ruris-te400-pds-57-720-480-0-0-154.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Brush Cutters</category>
      <price_with_vat>32.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>40012016am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001655</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS TE400 electric grass trimmer handles lawn finishing and edging on small and medium-sized areas. Its 400 W motor runs at 14,000 rpm for a clean cut over a 20 cm width, with line fed out progressively and automatically. Ultra-light (1.2 kg) and fitted with a telescopic shaft and an ergonomic handle, it effortlessly reaches edges, foundations and tight corners.

• Fast, clean cutting: 400 W electric motor at 14,000 rpm for efficient lawn care and neat finishing work.
• Precise in tricky areas: 200 mm cutting width, ideal along edges and foundations and around flower beds.
• Adjustable telescopic shaft: length adapts to your height and working position for greater comfort.
• Ultra-light: only 1.2 kg for effortless handling and reduced fatigue, even during extended use.
• Automatic line feed: progressive cutting-line release system and ergonomic handle for full control, plugs straight into the mains.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>50023217am</id>
      <name>RURIS TE500 PIVOT – Electric Grass Trimmer 500 W, 300 mm Cutting Width, Pivoting Head,
        Telescopic</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/intretinere-gazon/trimmer-electric-ruris-te500-pivot-194</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/trimmer-electric-ruris-te500-pivot-pds-57-720-480-0-0-194.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Brush Cutters</category>
      <price_with_vat>42.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>50023217am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739001662</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS TE500 PIVOT electric grass trimmer takes care of hard-to-reach areas: edges, paving joints and the ground around shrubs. Its 500 W motor at 14,000 rpm and pivoting dual-line head deliver a clean 300 mm cut at different angles, without constant repositioning. Telescopic adjustment and an ergonomic handle guarantee optimal comfort on mains power.

• Effective power: 500 W electric motor with a rotation speed of 14,000 rpm for fast, clean grass cutting.
• Pivoting dual-line head: pivots in two directions to trim precisely at any angle, around shrubs and along paths.
• Wide cutting swath: 300 mm width to quickly finish edges and areas the lawn mower cannot reach.
• Comfortable to use: telescopic length adjustment and ergonomic handle to suit your working position.
• Precision and smoothness: reduced vibration and automatic return of the cutting head to its initial position after use.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>20240rur26b</id>
      <name>RURIS 2024e – Cordless Grass Trimmer, 300 mm Cutting Width, Lightweight 1.7 kg, 20V 4Ah
        USB-C Battery Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/trimmer-ruris-2024e-569</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/trimmer-ruris-2024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-569.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>70.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>20240rur26b</mpn>
      <ean>5940739034691</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2024e is a lightweight (1.7 kg) cordless grass trimmer designed for lawn finishing around flower beds, trees and paths. It offers a 300 mm cutting diameter with 1.6 mm line and a rotating loop handle to adjust the working angle. RURIS ALFA UP 20V 4Ah Li-Ion battery included, with bidirectional USB-C charging: it recharges from any USB-C port and also works as a power bank. No mains charger needed.

• Precise, effortless finishing: 300 mm cutting diameter with 1.6 mm line for clean edges along paths, flower beds and trees, where the mower cannot reach.
• Ultra-light and manoeuvrable: only 1.7 kg with a rotating loop handle that lets you adjust the cutting angle to the terrain and your working position.
• 20V 4Ah battery included: RURIS ALFA UP 2400e Li-Ion battery with 3-level LED display, supplied with the tool so you can work straight out of the box.
• Bidirectional USB-C charging: recharges from any USB-C port (computer, phone charger, car) and doubles as a power bank for your mobile devices.
• Box contents: 2024e grass trimmer, 20V 4Ah USB-C battery, USB-C cable, 1.6 mm line head — no mains charger required.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>70000ZFR25A</id>
      <name>RURIS FP7 – Manual Fruit Crusher, 7 L Stainless Steel Hopper, Aluminium Rollers, Apples
        and Pears, 7.2 kg</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/zdrobitoare-fructe-si-struguri/zdrobitor-pentru-fructe-ruris-fp7-814</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/zdrobitor-pentru-fructe-ruris-fp7-pds-106-1920-1024-0-0-814_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/zdrobitor-pentru-fructe-ruris-fp7-pds-106-1920-1024-0-0-814_5.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Agriculture &gt; Fruit Crushers</category>
      <price_with_vat>69.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>70000ZFR25A</mpn>
      <ean>5940739008616</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS FP7 manual fruit crusher quickly processes generous quantities of apples, pears and other soft, stone-free fruit while preserving their natural quality. Its 7-litre stainless steel hopper resists corrosion, does not retain odours and does not alter the taste, while the aluminium rollers ensure uniform, gentle crushing. Compact (35 x 35 x 29 cm) and light at 7.2 kg, it fits in at the orchard as well as in the garden.

• 7 L stainless steel hopper: hygienic and corrosion-resistant, it retains no odours and preserves the authentic taste of the fruit.
• Gentle crushing: aluminium rollers that ensure uniform crushing, respecting the structure of the fruit and the texture of the juice.
• Manual crank operation: full control over the crushing, no motor, meaning minimal maintenance and long service life.
• Compact and light: 35 x 35 x 29 cm at 7.2 kg, easy to carry and store, ideal for small spaces, the orchard or the garden.
• Purpose-built: designed for apples, pears and soft, stone-free fruit, perfect for making homemade juice, cider and compotes.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>80240rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 8024e – Cordless Pressure Washer 20V, 30 bar, Self-Priming, without Battery</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/aparat-de-splat-cu-presiune-pe-acumulator-ruris-8024e-865</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-pressure-washer-ruris-8024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-865.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-pressure-washer-ruris-8024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-865_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>58.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>80240rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020403</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 8024e is a fully autonomous 20V brushless cordless pressure washer: its self-priming system with float draws water from a bucket, a canister or any open container. With 30 bar of pressure and a flow rate of 5 L/min, it washes cars, bikes, garden furniture and tools anywhere, with no power socket or tap needed. Ultra-compact (1.5 kg), it comes in a carrying case, without battery or charger. Compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V.

• 30 bar without a cord: 20V brushless motor delivering 30 bar and 5 L/min to wash cars, bikes, furniture and tools anywhere, with no power socket or water supply.
• Float-assisted self-priming: draws water directly from a bucket, canister or tank, ideal for camping, in the field or on the move.
• Ultra-compact: only 1.5 kg with a carrying case included, easy to take along in the boot of the car.
• Practical every day: instant trigger start, quiet operation and minimal maintenance.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, to be ordered separately; one battery for all your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1210rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1210 – Cordless SDS Plus Rotary Hammer 20V, 1.5 J, 900 rpm, LED, without
        Battery or Charger</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-604</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-604.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx1210-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-604_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1210rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739067996</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1210 cordless rotary hammer drills into concrete and masonry without a cable thanks to its SDS Plus chuck and 1.5 J of impact energy. With 900 rpm and 5100 blows/min, it drills concrete up to 16 mm, wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm. Compact (1.4 kg), with variable speed, forward/reverse switch and LED light. Supplied with 3 drill bits (8/10/12 mm), without battery or charger.

• Effective impact: 1.5 J of impact energy with 900 rpm and 5100 blows/min to drill concrete up to 16 mm, wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm.
• Two working modes: plain drilling or hammer drilling, with an SDS Plus chuck for fast, tool-free bit changes.
• Precise control: variable-speed trigger and rotation direction switch for drilling, driving screws and freeing jammed bits.
• Light and handy: only 1.4 kg with a built-in LED light, ideal for working at height or in poorly lit areas.
• Supplied without battery or charger: bare tool with 3 SDS Plus drill bits (8/10/12 mm), compatible with RURIS 20V batteries from the ALFA UP range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2813rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX2813 – Brushless SDS Plus Rotary Hammer 20V, 2.8 J, without Battery or Charger</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/search/rmx2813</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx2813-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-605.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ciocan-rotopercutor-ruris-rmx2813-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-605_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>85.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2813rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068009</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX2813 cordless rotary hammer combines a 20V brushless motor with an SDS Plus chuck for heavy-duty work. With 2.8 J of impact energy, 1150 rpm and 5100 blows/min, it drills concrete up to 26 mm, wood up to 30 mm and metal up to 13 mm. Four modes: drilling, hammer drilling, chiselling and Variolock for positioning the chisel. Supplied with 3 drill bits (8/10/12 mm) and a depth stop, without battery or charger.

• High impact power: 2.8 J of impact energy, 1150 rpm and 5100 blows/min to drill concrete up to 26 mm, wood up to 30 mm and metal up to 13 mm.
• 4 working modes: drilling, hammer drilling, chiselling and Variolock to lock the chisel at the optimal angle, without constant repositioning.
• 20V brushless motor: higher efficiency, less wear and long service life, with the power of a corded rotary hammer without the cable.
• Precise, comfortable work: depth stop, variable speed and LED light for consistent drilling, even in dark areas.
• Supplied without battery or charger: bare tool with 3 SDS Plus drill bits (8/10/12 mm) and a depth stop, compatible with RURIS 20V ALFA UP batteries.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>26240rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 2624e – Cordless Chainsaw 20V, 30 cm Bar, SDS Tensioning, without Battery or
        Charger</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2624e-867</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2624e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-867.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-869.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>95.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>26240rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020380</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2624e is a 20V cordless chainsaw running at 3600 rpm, fitted with a 30 cm bar giving a cutting length of 275 mm, ideal for pruning and small-diameter wood. The SDS tensioning system adjusts the chain without tools, and automatic lubrication (210 ml reservoir) protects the chain continuously. Compatible with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V battery. Supplied without battery or charger.

• Clean battery-powered cutting: 20V motor at 3600 rpm with a 30 cm bar and 275 mm cutting length, for pruning and cutting small-diameter wood.
• Tool-free adjustment: the SDS tensioning system lets you adjust the chain in seconds, right on the job.
• Automatic lubrication: 210 ml oil reservoir providing continuous protection of the chain and bar for extended service life.
• Quiet and light: instant trigger start, with no starter cord, fuel mix or exhaust fumes; perfect for everyday garden work.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with the RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V battery, to be ordered separately; one battery for all your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>27440rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 2744e – Brushless Cordless Chainsaw 40V, 400 mm Bar, 25 m/s, without Battery or
        Charger</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-869</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-869_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2744e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-869.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>119.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>27440rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020465</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2744e is a brushless 40V (2x20V) cordless chainsaw equipped with a 400 mm bar and a chain running at 25 m/s, for fast, precise cuts on trunks up to 395 mm. Its 2-speed variable trigger, tool-free SDS tensioner and dual chain brake provide control and safety in every situation. Supplied without battery or charger.

• 40V brushless power: 400 mm bar and 25 m/s chain to fell and cut trunks up to 395 mm, with the output of a light petrol chainsaw.
• Full control: 2-speed variable trigger to match the cut to the wood, from fine limbing to bucking firewood.
• Tool-free maintenance: SDS system to tension the chain and change the bar in seconds, right in the field.
• Safety and comfort: dual chain brake and vibration reduced to 1.76 m/s² for extended cutting sessions with complete peace of mind.
• Without battery or charger: bare tool, requires 2 RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries; share the batteries from your other RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>28440rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 2844e – Cordless Brushless Chainsaw 40V, 30 cm Bar, 3.8 kg, Battery Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-871</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-871_1.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electroferastrau-acumulator-ruris-2844e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-871.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>139.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>28440rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020472</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 2844e is an ultra-light 40V (2x20V) brushless cordless chainsaw: just 3.8 kg for maximum manoeuvrability when pruning and trimming trees. Its 30 cm bar delivers a cutting length of 285 mm, the SDS system adjusts the chain without tools and the double chain brake enhances safety. Compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V batteries. Supplied without batteries or charger.

• Ultra-light at 3.8 kg: one of the lightest 40V brushless chainsaws in its class, for pruning and trimming at height without fatigue.
• Efficient cutting: brushless 2x20V (40V) motor, 30 cm bar and 285 mm cutting length, suited to everyday garden maintenance work.
• Tool-free SDS tensioning: instant chain adjustment in the field, with no wrench or screwdriver required.
• Enhanced safety: double chain brake and optimal machine balance to reduce risk and fatigue during extended work.
• Sold without batteries or charger: requires 2 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V batteries, ordered separately; share batteries across your RURIS 20V tool range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>60640rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS VoltX 6064e – Cordless Brushless Hedge Trimmer 60V, 650 mm Blade, Battery and
        Charger Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/electrofoarfeca-ruris-voltx-6064e-858</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/electrofoarfeca-ruris-voltx-6064e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-858.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/electrofoarfeca-ruris-voltx-6064e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-858_4.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>169.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>60640rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020557</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS VoltX 6064e is a 60V brushless cordless hedge trimmer whose 650 mm (26 inch) dual-action blade cuts branches up to 30 mm in diameter without jamming. Its rear handle rotates into 5 positions for easy horizontal, angled and vertical cuts without straining your wrists, and its multifunction display shows battery level and speed. Weight: 3.75 kg. Supplied without battery or charger.

• 60V brushless power: 650 mm (26 inch) dual-action blade cutting branches up to 30 mm in diameter, with performance close to a petrol hedge trimmer.
• 5-position rotating handle: cut horizontally, at an angle or vertically without twisting your wrists or changing your posture.
• Multifunction display: check battery level and the selected speed at a glance to match your cutting to the density of the hedge.
• Light and manoeuvrable: only 3.75 kg with a low-vibration dual-action blade, for maintaining tall hedges and thick shrubs without fatigue.
• Battery and charger not included: tool sold alone, compatible with the RURIS VoltX 60V range; ALFA UP 6400e battery and 64e charger ordered separately.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>3140rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3140 – Cordless Circular Saw 20V, 140 mm Blade, 50 mm Cutting Depth, Battery
        and Charger Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-602</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-602.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-circular-ruris-rmx3140-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-602_1.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>69.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>3140rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068047</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3140 cordless circular saw with 20V brushless motor spins at 6800 rpm with a 140 mm blade, cutting wood and panels up to 50 mm deep. Adjustable angle from 0 to 45° for bevel cuts, graduated base plate, width limiter and LED light, all at just 1.8 kg. Supplied with a 140 mm blade, without battery or charger: compatible with ALFA UP 20V.

• 6800 rpm brushless motor: 140 mm blade for clean, fast cuts in wood and panels, with no cord and no power socket.
• Ideal for DIY and home improvement: cuts boards, skirting, panels and battens on the move, even at height thanks to its 1.8 kg weight.
• Precise, adjustable cuts: depth up to 50 mm, angle adjustable from 0 to 45°, graduated base plate and width limiter for straight and bevel cuts.
• Comfort and visibility: LED light for poorly lit areas and a lightweight grip for working longer without fatigue.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with all RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, ordered separately; supplied with a 140 mm blade fitted.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>3260rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3260 – Cordless Brushless Jigsaw 20V, 3800 rpm, LED, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-603</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-603.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ferastrau-pendular-ruris-rmx3260-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-603_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>79.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>3260rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068054</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3260 cordless jigsaw makes precise cuts in wood, metal and plastic thanks to its 20V brushless motor running at 3800 rpm. Its 5 speeds plus automatic mode, 4 pendulum positions and adjustable angle up to 45° adapt to every material. Easy Lock system, LED light and 4 blades included. Supplied without battery or charger, compatible with RURIS 20V batteries.

• Powerful 20V brushless motor: up to 3800 rpm and a 26 mm blade stroke for fast, clean cuts in wood, metal, plastic and aluminium.
• Versatile settings: 5 speeds plus automatic mode and 4 pendulum positions to match the cut to each material, with a tilt angle of up to 45° left and right.
• Tool-free blade change: Easy Lock system to swap blades in seconds, with a dust blower to keep the cutting line visible.
• Comfort and precision: built-in LED light and a balanced grip for curved or detailed cuts, even in poorly lit areas.
• Supplied without battery or charger: bare tool with 4 blades (100 x 1.5 x 45 mm), compatible with RURIS 20V batteries from the ALFA UP range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>30024rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 30024e – Portable Power Station 300 W, AC 240V, USB-C, DC 12V, LED Lamp, Batteries
        Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/invertor-portabil-ruris-30024e-873</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/invertor-portabil-ruris-30024e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-873.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>121.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>30024rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020410</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 30024e is a 300 W portable inverter that automatically switches from one battery to the next with no interruption, and also works as a quad charger when plugged into the mains. Its AC 240V, USB-C 18W, 2x USB-A and DC 12V/5A outputs power several devices at once, and its 7.2 W LED lamp comes to the rescue when camping or during power cuts. Supplied without batteries (takes up to 4 ALFA UP 2400e batteries).

• 300 W power station: powers your devices at 230 V from RURIS 20V batteries, with automatic switching between batteries and no interruption.
• Practical 2-in-1: plugged into the mains, it becomes a quad charger and recharges up to 4 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e batteries simultaneously with no separate chargers.
• Portable power strip: AC 240V, USB-C 18W fast-charge, 2x USB-A 5V/2A and DC 12V/5A outputs to run several devices at the same time.
• Built-in 7.2 W LED lamp: instant emergency lighting for camping, the worksite or power outages.
• Sold without batteries: complete it with up to 4 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V 4Ah batteries; reuse the batteries from your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1390rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1390 – Cordless Drill Driver 20V 130 Nm, 3-16 mm Chuck, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-multifunctionala-ruris-rmx1390-599</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-multifunctional-drill-ruris-rmx1390-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-599.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-multifunctional-drill-ruris-rmx1390-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-599_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>76.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1390rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068078</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1390 multifunction cordless drill driver with 20V brushless motor delivers 130 Nm, drilling metal up to 13 mm and wood up to 150 mm with the supplied earth auger bit. 2 speeds (0-300 / 0-1200 rpm), 3-16 mm chuck, side handle mountable in 3 positions and LED. Supplied with an 80x300 mm earth auger bit, D-handle and drill bit set, without battery or charger: compatible with ALFA UP 20V.

• High 130 Nm torque: brushless motor capable of drilling metal up to 13 mm and wood up to 150 mm with the supplied earth auger bit.
• Multifunctional: heavy-duty drilling and screwdriving in wood and metal, including deep holes for posts and planting thanks to the 80x300 mm earth auger bit.
• 2 speeds and 3-16 mm chuck: slow high-torque speed (0-300 rpm) for hard materials, fast speed (0-1200 rpm) for everyday drilling.
• Secure grip: side handle mountable in 3 positions, D-handle with extension and LED light for dark areas; weight 2.4 kg.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries; supplied with chuck key, adapter, 80x300 mm earth auger bit, D-handle and a set of metal and wood drill bits.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1360rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1360 – Cordless Brushless Hammer Drill Driver 20V, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-cu-percutie-ruris-rmx1360-598</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-drillscrewdriver-ruris-rmx1360-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-598.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-drillscrewdriver-ruris-rmx1360-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-598_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1360rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068085</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1360 cordless hammer drill driver with 20V brushless motor combines 3 functions: drilling, screwdriving and hammer drilling for brick and lightweight concrete. Its torque adjustment ring protects screws and materials, and its keyless chuck speeds up accessory changes. Compact, with LED light, it is sold without battery or charger: compatible with ALFA UP 20V.

• 3 functions in 1: drilling, screwdriving and hammer drilling for working wood, metal, brick and lightweight concrete without changing tools.
• 20V brushless motor: better efficiency and longer life than brushed motors, for regular use in all-round DIY.
• Torque adjustment: adjustment ring to protect screws and materials, plus a switchable hammer mode for light masonry.
• Practical and manoeuvrable: keyless chuck, LED light for dark areas and a compact, cord-free format.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with all RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, ordered separately; share a single battery across your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1260rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1260 – Cordless Brushless Drill Driver 20V 60 Nm, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1260-597</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx1260-cordless-drill-screwdriver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-597.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx1260-cordless-drill-screwdriver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-597_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>49.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1260rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068092</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1260 cordless drill driver with 20V brushless motor delivers a maximum torque of 60 Nm for drilling and screwdriving in wood, metal and plastic. Its 2 speeds (0-450 / 0-2000 rpm), 20+1 torque settings and 0-10 mm metal chuck guarantee precision and comfort, with LED. Supplied with 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm), without battery or charger: compatible with ALFA UP 20V.

• 60 Nm torque and brushless motor: drills and drives in wood, metal and plastic with efficiency and durability superior to brushed motors.
• Versatile for everyday use: perfect for DIY, furniture assembly and fixing jobs, at home or in the workshop.
• Precise control: 2 speeds (0-450 / 0-2000 rpm) and 20+1 torque settings to protect screws and materials; keyless 0-10 mm metal chuck.
• Light and comfortable: only 0.88 kg, with LED light and charge indicator for working easily in dark areas.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries; supplied with 5 screwdriver bits and 7 drill bits (3-10 mm).]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>1240rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX1240 – Cordless Drill Driver 20V 40 Nm, 2 Speeds, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-596</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-596.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/masina-de-gaurit-insurubat-ruris-rmx1240-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-596_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>39.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>1240rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068108</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX1240 cordless drill driver with 20V brushless motor develops 40 Nm of torque, drilling wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm. Its 2 speeds (0-400 / 0-1350 rpm), 20+1 torque settings and 0-10 mm metal chuck ensure precise screwdriving, with LED light. Supplied with 8 bits, 8 drill bits, magnetic adapter and countersink bit, without battery or charger.

• 40 Nm torque and brushless motor: drills wood up to 25 mm and metal up to 10 mm, with efficiency and lifespan superior to brushed motors.
• Versatile for everyday use: ideal for drilling and screwdriving in DIY and intensive use alike, in wood, metal and plastic.
• Precise control: 2 speeds (0-400 / 0-1350 rpm) and 20+1 torque settings to protect screws and materials; keyless 0-10 mm metal chuck.
• Comfortable to use: LED light for dark areas and a low weight of 0.94 kg for working long hours without fatigue.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries; supplied with 8 screwdriver bits, 8 drill bits (2-6 mm), magnetic adapter and countersink bit.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>2300rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX2300 – Cordless Impact Driver 20V 230 Nm, 1/4 Hex, Battery and Charger Not
        Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-insurubat-cu-impact-ruris-rmx2300-600</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-impact-driver-ruris-rmx2300-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-600.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/cordless-impact-driver-ruris-rmx2300-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-600_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>52.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>2300rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068115</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX2300 cordless impact driver with 20V brushless motor delivers 230 Nm, 3300 rpm and 4500 impacts per minute to drive and remove M8 to M18 screws effortlessly. 1/4 inch hex drive, torque adjustable across 3 levels, Reversal Stop function and LED light, all at just 0.94 kg. Sold without battery or charger, it is compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries.

• 230 Nm torque and brushless motor: 3300 rpm and 4500 impacts per minute to drive bolts and long M8-M18 screws where a standard drill driver stalls.
• Ideal for assembling structures, construction and mechanics: ultra-compact 0.94 kg format to reach tight spaces and drive screw after screw.
• 1/4 inch (6.35 mm) hex drive: quick bit changes; torque adjustable across 3 levels and Reversal Stop function to avoid damaging screws.
• Comfort and control: LED light and charge indicator for working precisely, even in dark areas.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with all RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, ordered separately; share a single battery across your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>3500rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX3500 – Cordless Impact Wrench 20V 350 Nm, 1/2 Square Drive, Battery and Charger
        Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/masina-de-insurubat-cu-impact-ruris-rmx3500-601</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx3500-cordless-impact-driver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-601.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx3500-cordless-impact-driver-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-601_3.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>59.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>3500rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068122</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX3500 cordless impact wrench with 20V brushless motor develops an extreme torque of 350 Nm, 0-2400 rpm and 3300 impacts per minute for heavy-duty bolting and M8 to M18 screws. Its 1/2 inch square drive accepts standard impact sockets; torque adjustable across 3 levels, Reversal Stop and LED. Sold without battery or charger, compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries.

• Extreme 350 Nm torque: brushless motor at 3300 impacts per minute to tighten and loosen large bolts up to M18 without effort.
• Ideal for car mechanics, bolting and construction: frees wheels, seized nuts and stuck fasteners.
• 1/2 inch square drive: compatible with standard impact sockets; torque adjustable across 3 levels and Reversal Stop function for precise control.
• Compact and comfortable: only 1 kg, with LED light and charge indicator for working efficiently anywhere.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with all RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, ordered separately; share a single battery across your RURIS 20V tools.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>31440rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 3144e – Cordless Brushless Brush Cutter 40V, Trimmer Line + 3-Tooth Blade, Battery
        and Charger Not Included</name>
      <link>
        https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motocoasa-de-umar-pe-acumulator-ruris-3144e-872</link>
      <image>
        https://www.ruris.ro/motocoasa-de-umar-pe-acumulator-ruris-3144e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-872.jpg</image>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>109.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>31440rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020441</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 3144e is a cordless brush cutter with a 40V (2x20V) brushless motor offering torque comparable to entry-level petrol models, with no fuel and no engine maintenance. Its dual cutting system — a 300 mm line head and a 255 mm 3-tooth blade — moves from edge finishing to woody undergrowth. Practical modular shaft for easy transport. Supplied without battery or charger.

• 40V brushless power: the torque of a light petrol brush cutter from two 20V batteries, with no fuel, no fumes and minimal maintenance.
• Dual cutting system: 300 mm line head for finishing and edging, 255 mm 3-tooth blade for tall grass and woody vegetation.
• Modular shaft: splits into two parts for easy transport in the boot and storage at home.
• Comfortable to use: only 4.97 kg, with no pull-start and none of the vibrations of a petrol engine, so you can work longer without fatigue.
• Battery and charger not included: tool sold alone, requires 2 RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries; ideal if you already own batteries from the 20V range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>40440rur26a</id>
      <name>RURIS 4044e – Cordless Brushless Tiller 40V, 30 cm Working Width, Battery and Charger
        Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/produse-pe-acumulatori/motosapa-pe-acumulator-ruris-4044e-868</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/battery-powered-tiller-ruris-4044e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-868.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/battery-powered-tiller-ruris-4044e-pds-80-1920-1024-0-0-868_5.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Garden &gt; Battery-Powered Garden Machines</category>
      <price_with_vat>139.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>40440rur26a</mpn>
      <ean>5940739020434</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS 4044e is a compact, lightweight (9.65 kg) cordless tiller powered by a 40V (2x20V) brushless motor. With a working width of 30 cm and a depth of 20 cm, it quickly loosens the soil in vegetable gardens, greenhouses and flower beds, with no cord and no fuel. Its very low vibrations (0.78 m/s²) and instant start make it a pleasure to use. Compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V. Supplied without batteries or charger.

• Cordless electric tiller: 40V (2x20V) brushless motor that loosens and prepares the soil with no fuel, cord or exhaust fumes.
• Ideal for vegetable gardens and greenhouses: 30 cm working width and 20 cm depth, perfect for previously cultivated soil, flower beds and small plots.
• Remarkable comfort: very low vibrations of 0.78 m/s² and a contained weight of 9.65 kg for tilling long sessions without fatigue.
• Ready in an instant: immediate trigger start, with no pull cord or petrol mix, and maintenance kept to a minimum.
• Sold without batteries or charger: requires 2 RURIS ALFA UP 2400e 20V batteries, ordered separately; share batteries across your RURIS 20V tool range.]]></description>
    </product>
    <product>
      <id>4125rmx2024am</id>
      <name>RURIS RMX4125 – Cordless Angle Grinder 20V, 125 mm Disc, 8500 rpm, Battery and Charger
        Not Included</name>
      <link>https://www.ruris.ro/pe-acumulatori/polizor-unghiular-ruris-rmx4125-606</link>
      <image>https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx4125-angle-grinder-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-606.jpg</image>
      <additional_imageurl>
        https://www.ruris.ro/ruris-rmx4125-angle-grinder-pds-88-1920-1024-0-0-606_2.jpg</additional_imageurl>
      <category>Tools &gt; Cordless Power Tools</category>
      <price_with_vat>62.99</price_with_vat>
      <vat>24</vat>
      <availability>1-3</availability>
      <manufacturer>RURIS</manufacturer>
      <mpn>4125rmx2024am</mpn>
      <ean>5940739068191</ean>
      <instock>Y</instock>
      <quantity>10</quantity>
      <description><![CDATA[The RURIS RMX4125 cordless angle grinder with 20V brushless motor cuts and grinds metal and stone with its 125 mm disc and 2 speeds (2600 and 8500 rpm). A disc lock button, adjustable protective guard and charge indicator provide safety and comfort at just 1.6 kg. Supplied with a 125 mm disc and auxiliary handle, without battery or charger: compatible with ALFA UP 20V.

• 2-speed brushless motor: 2600 rpm for sanding and finishing, 8500 rpm for cutting, with a 125 mm disc compatible with standard accessories.
• Versatile and mobile: cuts and grinds metal and stone anywhere, with no cord or socket, where a corded grinder is limited.
• Quick accessory change: disc lock button and a protective guard with adjustable position for working safely.
• Light and manoeuvrable: only 1.6 kg, with a 2-position auxiliary handle and a charge indicator for constant monitoring.
• Sold without battery or charger: compatible with RURIS ALFA UP 20V batteries, ordered separately; supplied with a 125 mm disc and auxiliary handle.]]></description>
    </product>
  </products>
</mywebstore>
